[
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "Adam",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا آدَمُ",
        "answer": "O Adam",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yāādamu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِآدَمَ",
        "answer": "to Adam",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "liādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا آدَمُ",
        "answer": "O Adam",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yāādamu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "آدَمُ",
        "answer": "Adam",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ādamu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "ever",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(with) Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْلِيسَ",
        "answer": "Iblis",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ib'līsa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَائِكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your forefathers",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ābāika",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "our forefathers (following)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ābāanā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاؤُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their forefathers",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ābāuhum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your forefathers",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ābāakum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَىٰ",
        "answer": "He refused",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "abā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْبَ",
        "answer": "(should) refuse",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaba",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْبَ",
        "answer": "(should) refuse",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaba",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتُوا",
        "answer": "then produce",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fatū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُتُوا",
        "answer": "And they will be given",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-utū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "comes to you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yatiyannakum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they come to you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yatūkum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَأْتِ",
        "answer": "We bring",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nati",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَ",
        "answer": "brings",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yatiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِينَا",
        "answer": "comes to us",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tatīnā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَيْتَ",
        "answer": "you come",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "atayta",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِ",
        "answer": "will bring",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yati",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتُوا",
        "answer": "you come",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tatū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأْتُوا",
        "answer": "And come",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "watū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَهُمُ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yatiyahumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "(has) come to you",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yatikum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "then come to them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "fatūhunna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتُوا",
        "answer": "so come",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fatū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَكُمُ",
        "answer": "will come to you",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yatiyakumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yatiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِي",
        "answer": "brings up",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yatī",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتِ",
        "answer": "so you bring",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fati",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِينَكَ",
        "answer": "they will come to you",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yatīnaka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتُوا",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "waātū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We have given you",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "ātaynākum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتُوا",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "waātū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We gave",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "waātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We gave you",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "ātaynākum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "were given",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتُوا",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "waātū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "We have given them",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "was given",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "was given",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "were given",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "were given",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "We gave [them]",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَى",
        "answer": "and gives",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "waātā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَى",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "waātā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتِنَا",
        "answer": "Grant us",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "ātinā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتِنَا",
        "answer": "Grant us",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "ātinā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We gave them",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوهُ",
        "answer": "were given it",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "ūtūhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْتُمُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "you have given them",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "ātaytumūhunna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you give",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "ātaytum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتَ",
        "answer": "he has been given",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "yu'ta",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتِي",
        "answer": "gives",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "yu'tī",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَاهُ",
        "answer": "and gave him",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "waātāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We gave",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "waātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاهُ",
        "answer": "gave him",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "ātāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآتَتْ",
        "answer": "so it yielded",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "faātat",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتِي",
        "answer": "He grants",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "yu'tī",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتَ",
        "answer": "is granted",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "yu'ta",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "he is granted",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُؤْتُوهَا",
        "answer": "and give it",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "watu'tūhā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَوُا",
        "answer": "and gave",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "waātawū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْإِثْمِ",
        "answer": "in sin",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bil-ith'mi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِثْمَ",
        "answer": "sin",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ith'ma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِثْمُهُ",
        "answer": "its sin",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ith'muhu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِثْمًا",
        "answer": "sin",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ith'man",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِثْمَ",
        "answer": "sin",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ith'ma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْإِثْمِ",
        "answer": "sinfully",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bil-ith'mi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِثْمَ",
        "answer": "sin",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ith'ma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِثْمَ",
        "answer": "sin",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ith'ma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْإِثْمِ",
        "answer": "to [the] sins",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "bil-ith'mi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِثْمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a sin",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ith'mun",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِثْمُهُمَا",
        "answer": "But sin of both of them",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wa-ith'muhumā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثِيمٍ",
        "answer": "sinner",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "athīmin",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "آثِمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) sinful ",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "āthimun",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their reward",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ajruhum",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرُهُ",
        "answer": "(is) his reward",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ajruhu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their reward",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ajruhum",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their reward",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ajruhum",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their reward",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ajruhum",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "their (waiting) term",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ajalahunna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "their (waiting) term",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ajalahunna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "their (specified) term",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ajalahunna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلَهُ",
        "answer": "its end",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ajalahu",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلٍ",
        "answer": "a term",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ajalin",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلِهِ",
        "answer": "its term",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ajalihi",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(each) one of them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aḥaduhum",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "any",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدَكُمُ",
        "answer": "any of you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "aḥadakumu",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدُكُمْ",
        "answer": "any of you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "aḥadukum",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "any",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِحْدَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "one of the two",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "iḥ'dāhumā",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِحْدَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "one of the two",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "iḥ'dāhumā",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْخَذُ",
        "answer": "will be taken",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yu'khadhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذَتْكُمُ",
        "answer": "So seized you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhatkumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "We took",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُذُوا",
        "answer": "Hold",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khudhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "We took",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "We took",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "We took",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُذُوا",
        "answer": "Hold",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "khudhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذَتْهُ",
        "answer": "takes him",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "akhadhathu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْخُذُوا",
        "answer": "you take (back)",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "takhudhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْخُذُهُ",
        "answer": "overtakes Him",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "takhudhuhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخُذْ",
        "answer": "Then take",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fakhudh",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤَاخِذُكُمُ",
        "answer": "will take you to task",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "yuākhidhukumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤَاخِذُكُمْ",
        "answer": "He takes you to task",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "yuākhidhukum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤَاخِذْنَا",
        "answer": "take us to task",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "tuākhidh'nā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you took",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhtumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَتَّخِذُنَا",
        "answer": "Do you take us",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "atattakhidhunā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَّخَذْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Have you taken",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "attakhadhtum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you took",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhtumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذَ",
        "answer": "has taken",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "ittakhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّخِذُوا",
        "answer": "and (said), \"Take",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "wa-ittakhidhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذُ",
        "answer": "takes",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "yattakhidhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّخِذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "tattakhidhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآخِذِيهِ",
        "answer": "take it",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "biākhidhīhi",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاتِّخَاذِكُمُ",
        "answer": "by your taking",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "bi-ittikhādhikumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأَخَّرَ",
        "answer": "delays",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ta-akhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "and in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wabil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "for the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "bil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "and the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wal-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "and the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wal-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "[the] Last",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "[the] Last",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةُ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiratu",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "the Last",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "[the] Last",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "[the] Last",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "[the] Last",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "[the] Last",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the other",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "l-ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخَرَ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "ukhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخَرَ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "ukhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخِيهِ",
        "answer": "his brother",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "akhīhi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِخْوَانُكُمْ",
        "answer": "then they (are) your brothers",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-ikh'wānukum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيُؤَدِّ",
        "answer": "then let discharge",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "falyu-addi",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَدَاءٌ",
        "answer": "[and] payment",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-adāon",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذِ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wa-idhi",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذِ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wa-idhi",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "But when",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and when",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "But when",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then when",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then when",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then when",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then when",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then when",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "(would) then",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْذَنُوا",
        "answer": "then be informed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fadhanū",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their ears",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ādhānihim",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِ",
        "answer": "by (the) permission",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'ni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِ",
        "answer": "by permission",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'ni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِهِ",
        "answer": "with His permission",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'nihi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِهِ",
        "answer": "by His permission",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'nihi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِ",
        "answer": "by (the) permission",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'ni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِ",
        "answer": "by (the) permission",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'ni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِهِ",
        "answer": "by His permission",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'nihi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذًى",
        "answer": "an ailment",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "adhan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذًى",
        "answer": "(is) a hurt",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "adhan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذًى",
        "answer": "hurt ",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "adhan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذًى",
        "answer": "(by) hurt",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "adhan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَذَىٰ",
        "answer": "or [the] hurt",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wal-adhā",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "(to) the earth",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the Earth",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْحَاقَ",
        "answer": "and Isaac ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-is'ḥāqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْحَاقَ",
        "answer": "and Isaac",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-is'ḥāqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْحَاقَ",
        "answer": "and Isaac",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-is'ḥāqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُسَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "(as) captives",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "usārā",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْمَاعِيلَ",
        "answer": "and Ishmael",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-is'māʿīla",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْمَاعِيلُ",
        "answer": "and Ishmael",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-is'māʿīlu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْمَاعِيلَ",
        "answer": "and Ishmael",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-is'māʿīla",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْمَاعِيلَ",
        "answer": "and Ishmael",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-is'māʿīla",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْمَاعِيلَ",
        "answer": "and Ishmael",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-is'māʿīla",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِصْرًا",
        "answer": "a burden",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "iṣ'ran",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلَا",
        "answer": "and [you both] eat",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wakulā",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكُلُوا",
        "answer": "then eat",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلُونَ",
        "answer": "they eat",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yakulūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلُوا",
        "answer": "And eat",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْكُلُوا",
        "answer": "eat",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "takulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَأْكُلُوا",
        "answer": "so that you may eat",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "litakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلُونَ",
        "answer": "consume",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yakulūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُكُلَهَا",
        "answer": "its harvest",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "ukulahā",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْفَ",
        "answer": "(of) a thousand",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "alfa",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُلُوفٌ",
        "answer": "(were in) thousands",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ulūfun",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "[except]",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "558",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "559",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "560",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "(do anything) except",
        "pcklId": "561",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "562",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "563",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "564",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "565",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "566",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "567",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "568",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "569",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "570",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "unless",
        "pcklId": "571",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "572",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "573",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "574",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "575",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "576",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "577",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "578",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "660",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) the ones who",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(of) the one who",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The One Who",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "whose",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) those who",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one which",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(that) which",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "that which",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِي",
        "answer": "for that which",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) the ones who",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "what",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those whom",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) those who",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(To) those whom",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(of) the one who",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) they who",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) the ones who",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) that",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "For those who",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(of) that which",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالَّذِي",
        "answer": "like the one who",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "ka-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالَّذِي",
        "answer": "like the one who",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "ka-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "278"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1442",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1443",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَكَ",
        "answer": "your God",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ilāhaka",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "and (the) God",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهًا",
        "answer": "God",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ilāhan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَٰهُكُمْ",
        "answer": "And your God",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-ilāhukum",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٌ",
        "answer": "(is) God",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ilāhun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "God",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "to Allah",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "but Allah",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "to Allah",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "[So] Allah",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "fal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "And for Allah",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "walillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "For Allah",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "belong to Allah",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "for Allah",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(belongs) to Allah",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "to Allah",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah (has)",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(set by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "192"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "for Allah",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "for Allah",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "202"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "207"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "207"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "209"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "298",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "299",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "300",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah (come)",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "307",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "308",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah ",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah s (name)",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "324",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "227"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "332",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "333",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "334",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah (is)",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "347",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "for Allah",
        "pcklId": "351",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "238"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "242"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "244"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "244"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah ",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "371",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "373",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "374",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "376",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "252"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "377",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah ",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "394",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "395",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "402",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "while Allah",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "404",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "410",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "411",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "412",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "413",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "414",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "415",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "278"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "416",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "417",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "418",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "419",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "420",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "421",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "422",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "425",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "To Allah (belongs)",
        "pcklId": "426",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "427",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "428",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "429",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "430",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْلُونَ",
        "answer": "swear (off)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yu'lūna",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to us",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "towards Him",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "into",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "followed",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "unto Him",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَى",
        "answer": "And to",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "[to]",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "[towards]",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "[towards]",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "towards you",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "until",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "and to You",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ami",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَرَ",
        "answer": "has ordered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "amara",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَأْمُرُونَ",
        "answer": "Do you order",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "atamurūna",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْمُرُكُمْ",
        "answer": "commands you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yamurukum",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْمَرُونَ",
        "answer": "you are commanded",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tu'marūna",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْمُرُكُمْ",
        "answer": "orders you (to do) it",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yamurukum",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْمُرُكُمْ",
        "answer": "he commands you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yamurukum",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَرَكُمُ",
        "answer": "has ordered you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "amarakumu",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَأْمُرُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and orders you",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wayamurukum",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْرِهِ",
        "answer": "His Command",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "bi-amrihi",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرًا",
        "answer": "a matter",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "amran",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْرُ",
        "answer": "the matter",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-amru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُمُورُ",
        "answer": "(all) the matters",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "l-umūru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمْرُهُ",
        "answer": "and his case",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "wa-amruhu",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِمَامًا",
        "answer": "a leader",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "imāman",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِّيُّونَ",
        "answer": "(are) unlettered ones",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ummiyyūna",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةً",
        "answer": "a community",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "ummatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٌ",
        "answer": "(was) a community",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "ummatun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٌ",
        "answer": "(was) a community",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ummatun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةً",
        "answer": "a community",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ummatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةً",
        "answer": "a community",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ummatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "Then as for",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "And as for",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِمَّا",
        "answer": "and when",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "fa-immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are secure",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "amintum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are secure",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "amintum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِنَ",
        "answer": "entrusts",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "amina",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believed",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنُوا",
        "answer": "Believe",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "āminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "Should we believe",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "anu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمِنُوا",
        "answer": "And believe",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "waāminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْمِنَ",
        "answer": "(will) we believe",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "nu'mina",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "they will believe",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We have believed",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَتُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "So do you believe",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "afatu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنُوا",
        "answer": "Believe",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "āminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "nu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "(had) believed",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We have believed",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "they believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have believed",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "āmantum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believes",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْيُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "and let them believe",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "walyu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنَّ",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "yu'minna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "yu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنَّ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "yu'minna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "believes",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "yu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُؤْمِنْ",
        "answer": "and believes",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "wayu'min",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْمِنْ",
        "answer": "you believed",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "tu'min",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "yu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "278"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe[d]",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "Believed",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "اؤْتُمِنَ",
        "answer": "is entrusted",
        "pcklId": "557",
        "tlit": "u'tumina",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَانَتَهُ",
        "answer": "his trust",
        "pcklId": "562",
        "tlit": "amānatahu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمْنًا",
        "answer": "and (a place of) security",
        "pcklId": "564",
        "tlit": "wa-amnan",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنًا",
        "answer": "secure",
        "pcklId": "590",
        "tlit": "āminan",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your faith",
        "pcklId": "604",
        "tlit": "īmānukum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْإِيمَانِ",
        "answer": "with [the] faith",
        "pcklId": "605",
        "tlit": "bil-īmāni",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your (having) faith",
        "pcklId": "606",
        "tlit": "īmānikum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your faith",
        "pcklId": "607",
        "tlit": "īmānakum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) believers (at all)",
        "pcklId": "649",
        "tlit": "bimu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "650",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "651",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "for the believers",
        "pcklId": "652",
        "tlit": "lil'mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) the believers",
        "pcklId": "653",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "654",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "655",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "278"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "and the believers",
        "pcklId": "656",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنٌ",
        "answer": "(who is) believing",
        "pcklId": "844",
        "tlit": "mu'minun",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنَةٌ",
        "answer": "(who is) believing",
        "pcklId": "873",
        "tlit": "mu'minatun",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَأَمَةٌ",
        "answer": "And a bondwoman",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wala-amatun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأُنْثَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the female",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-unthā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْأُنْثَىٰ",
        "answer": "for the female",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bil-unthā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنَاسٍ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "unāsin",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "How",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "How",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) People",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) People",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَهُ",
        "answer": "its people",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ahlahu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلُهُ",
        "answer": "his family",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ahluhu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهِ",
        "answer": "its people",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ahlihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَئُودُهُ",
        "answer": "tires Him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaūduhu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أُولِي",
        "answer": "O men",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "yāulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أُولِي",
        "answer": "O men",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "yāulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولُو",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "ulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "āli",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلَ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "āla",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلُ",
        "answer": "(by the) family",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "ālu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآلُ",
        "answer": "and family",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "waālu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَيَّدْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We supported him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ayyadnāhu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَيَّدْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We supported him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-ayyadnāhu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِي",
        "answer": "My Signs (for)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "biāyātī",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "in (the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Signs",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "Verses",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "āyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "āyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٌ",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "āyatun",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the signs",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِكَ",
        "answer": "Your Verses",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "āyātika",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٍ",
        "answer": "(the) signs",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "āyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our verses",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "surely (are) Signs",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "laāyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His verses",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٍ",
        "answer": "(the) Sign(s)",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "āyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] Verses",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Verses",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Verses",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Verses",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "242"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةَ",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "āyata",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَةً",
        "answer": "(is) surely a sign",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "laāyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتُ",
        "answer": "(are the) Verses",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "āyātu",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "252"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(His) Signs",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِئْسَمَا",
        "answer": "Evil (is) that",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bi'samā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِئْسَمَا",
        "answer": "Evil (is) that",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bi'samā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "And surely evil",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "walabi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "and evil",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wabi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "[and] surely an evil",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "walabi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَأْسِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] stress",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-basi",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَأْسَاءِ",
        "answer": "[the] suffering",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-basāi",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَأْسَاءُ",
        "answer": "[the] adversity",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-basāu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَثَّ",
        "answer": "and dispersing",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wabatha",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرَ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-baḥra",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْخَسْ",
        "answer": "diminish",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yabkhas",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدِيعُ",
        "answer": "(The) Originator",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "badīʿu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَدَّلَ",
        "answer": "But changed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fabaddala",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدَّلَهُ",
        "answer": "changes it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "baddalahu",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَدِّلُونَهُ",
        "answer": "alter it",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yubaddilūnahu",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَدِّلْ",
        "answer": "changes",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yubaddil",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَبَدَّلِ",
        "answer": "exchanges",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yatabaddali",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَسْتَبْدِلُونَ",
        "answer": "Would you exchange",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "atastabdilūna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْدُونَ",
        "answer": "you reveal",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "tub'dūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْدُوا",
        "answer": "you disclose",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tub'dū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْدُوا",
        "answer": "you disclose",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tub'dū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَرَّأَ",
        "answer": "will disown",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tabarra-a",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَتَبَرَّأَ",
        "answer": "then we will disown",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fanatabarra-a",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَرَّءُوا",
        "answer": "they disown",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tabarraū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَارِئِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Creator",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "bāri-ikum",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَارِئِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Creator",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "bāri-ikum",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَرُّوا",
        "answer": "you do good",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tabarrū",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبِرِّ",
        "answer": "[the] righteousness",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "bil-biri",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبِرَّ",
        "answer": "[the] righteousness",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-bira",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبِرَّ",
        "answer": "the righteous[ness]",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-bira",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبِرُّ",
        "answer": "[the] righteousness",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-biru",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبِرَّ",
        "answer": "[the] righteous",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-bira",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرَزُوا",
        "answer": "they went forth",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "barazū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَرْقٌ",
        "answer": "and lightning",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wabarqun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَرْقُ",
        "answer": "the lightning",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-barqu",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُرْهَانَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your proof",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bur'hānakum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَبْسُطُ",
        "answer": "and grants abundance",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayabṣuṭu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَسْطَةً",
        "answer": "abundantly",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "basṭatan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَشِّرِ",
        "answer": "And give good news",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wabashiri",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَشِّرِ",
        "answer": "but give good news",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wabashiri",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَشِّرِ",
        "answer": "And give glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wabashiri",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَاشِرُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "have relations with them",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "bāshirūhunna",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبَاشِرُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "have relations with them",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "tubāshirūhunna",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبُشْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "and glad tiding(s)",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "wabush'rā",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشِيرًا",
        "answer": "(as) a bearer of good news",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "bashīran",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبَشِّرِينَ",
        "answer": "(as) bearers of glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "mubashirīna",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) they see",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْصَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their vision",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "abṣārihim",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْصَارَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their sight",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "abṣārahum",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْصَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their sight",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wa-abṣārihim",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَصَلِهَا",
        "answer": "and its onions",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wabaṣalihā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْطِلُوا",
        "answer": "render in vain",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tub'ṭilū",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَاطِلِ",
        "answer": "with [the] falsehood",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bil-bāṭili",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَاطِلِ",
        "answer": "wrongfully",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "bil-bāṭili",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُطُونِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their bellies",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "buṭūnihim",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعَثْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We revived you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baʿathnākum",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْعَثْ",
        "answer": "[And] raise up",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'ʿath",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَعَثَ",
        "answer": "then raised up",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fabaʿatha",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْعَثْ",
        "answer": "Appoint",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ib'ʿath",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعَثَ",
        "answer": "raised",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "baʿatha",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعَثَهُ",
        "answer": "He raised him",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "baʿathahu",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِ",
        "answer": "after him",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "baʿdihi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِ",
        "answer": "after him",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "baʿdihi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِ",
        "answer": "after him",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "baʿdihi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِي",
        "answer": "after me",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "baʿdī",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "209"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدُ",
        "answer": "after (that)",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "baʿdu",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "baʿdihim",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَمَا",
        "answer": "after what",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "baʿdamā",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعِيدٍ",
        "answer": "far",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "baʿīdin",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُكُمْ",
        "answer": "some of you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baʿḍukum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "to others",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "libaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَعْضِهَا",
        "answer": "with a part of it",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bibaʿḍihā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "some (others)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَعْضِ",
        "answer": "in part (of)",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bibaʿḍi",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "in part",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "bibaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "(of each) other",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "baʿḍahum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "with others",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bibaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "baʿḍahum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "others",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "baʿḍahum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَ",
        "answer": "a part",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "baʿḍa",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُكُمْ",
        "answer": "one of you",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "baʿḍukum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضًا",
        "answer": "(to) another",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "baʿḍan",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعُوضَةً",
        "answer": "(of) a mosquito",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "baʿūḍatan",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبُعُولَتُهُنَّ",
        "answer": "And their husbands",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wabuʿūlatuhunna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْتَغُوا",
        "answer": "and seek",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'taghū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبْتَغُوا",
        "answer": "you seek",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "tabtaghū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْيًا",
        "answer": "grudging",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "baghyan",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْيًا",
        "answer": "(out of) jealousy",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "baghyan",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَاغٍ",
        "answer": "(being) disobedient",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "bāghin",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتِغَاءَ",
        "answer": "seeking",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "ib'tighāa",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "207"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتِغَاءَ",
        "answer": "seeking",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "ib'tighāa",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتِغَاءَ",
        "answer": "seeking",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "ib'tighāa",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَقَرَ",
        "answer": "[the] cows",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-baqara",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَقَرَةً",
        "answer": "a cow",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "baqaratan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَقَرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a cow",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "baqaratun",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَقَرَةٌ",
        "answer": "a cow",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "baqaratun",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَقَرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a cow",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "baqaratun",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَقْلِهَا",
        "answer": "its herbs",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baqlihā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَقِيَ",
        "answer": "remained",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baqiya",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "278"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَقِيَّةٌ",
        "answer": "and a remnant",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wabaqiyyatun",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكْرٌ",
        "answer": "young",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bik'run",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُكْمٌ",
        "answer": "dumb",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "buk'mun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُكْمٌ",
        "answer": "dumb",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "buk'mun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَدًا",
        "answer": "a city",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baladan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْلُغَ",
        "answer": "reaches",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yablugha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَلَغْنَ",
        "answer": "and they reach",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fabalaghna",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَلَغْنَ",
        "answer": "and they reached",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fabalaghna",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَغْنَ",
        "answer": "they reach",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "balaghna",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْلُغَ",
        "answer": "reaches",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yablugha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَنَبْلُوَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "And surely We will test you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "walanabluwannakum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتَلَىٰ",
        "answer": "tried",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ib'talā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَاءٌ",
        "answer": "(was) a trial",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "balāon",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبْتَلِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "will test you",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "mub'talīkum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْنَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your sons",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "abnāakum",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَ",
        "answer": "(the) son",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْنَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their sons",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "abnāahum",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْنَ",
        "answer": "and (of)",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْنِ",
        "answer": "and (of)",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'ni",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْنَائِنَا",
        "answer": "and our children",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wa-abnāinā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِنَاءً",
        "answer": "a canopy",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "bināan",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(from the) Children",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِيهِ",
        "answer": "(upon) his sons",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "banīhi",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِيَّ",
        "answer": "O my sons",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "yābaniyya",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَنِيهِ",
        "answer": "to his sons",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "libanīhi",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبُهِتَ",
        "answer": "So became dumbfounded",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fabuhita",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَاءُوا",
        "answer": "and they drew on themselves",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wabāū",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَاءُوا",
        "answer": "So they have drawn (on themselves)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fabāū",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَابَ",
        "answer": "the gate",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-bāba",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْوَابِهَا",
        "answer": "their doors",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "abwābihā",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيْتَ",
        "answer": "the House",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-bayta",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْتِيَ",
        "answer": "My House",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "baytiya",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيْتِ",
        "answer": "the House",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-bayti",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيْتَ",
        "answer": "(of) the House",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-bayta",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبُيُوتَ",
        "answer": "(to) the houses",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-buyūta",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبُيُوتَ",
        "answer": "(to) the houses",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-buyūta",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَبْيَضُ",
        "answer": "[the] white",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-abyaḍu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَايَعْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you make commercial transaction",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tabāyaʿtum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْعٌ",
        "answer": "bargaining",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bayʿun",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيْعُ",
        "answer": "the trade",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-bayʿu",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيْعَ",
        "answer": "[the] trade",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-bayʿa",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنْ",
        "answer": "to make clear",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yubayyin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنْ",
        "answer": "to make clear",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yubayyin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنْ",
        "answer": "to make clear",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yubayyin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيَّنَّا",
        "answer": "We have made clear",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bayyannā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيَّنَّاهُ",
        "answer": "We made clear",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "bayyannāhu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيَّنُوا",
        "answer": "and openly declar[ed]",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wabayyanū",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنُ",
        "answer": "makes clear",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yubayyinu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنُ",
        "answer": "makes clear",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yubayyinu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُبَيِّنُ",
        "answer": "And He makes clear",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wayubayyinu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنُهَا",
        "answer": "He makes them clear",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yubayyinuhā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنُ",
        "answer": "makes clear",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yubayyinu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "242"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنُ",
        "answer": "makes clear",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yubayyinu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "became clear",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "tabayyana",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَبَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "becomes distinct",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yatabayyana",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "has become distinct",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "tabayyana",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "became clear",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "tabayyana",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(in) front",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(was)",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "among yourselves",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "baynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among themselves",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between themselves",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "among you",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "baynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(is)",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "between you",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "baynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "among you",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "baynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] clear signs",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "l-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "with [the] clear signs",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "bil-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "the clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "l-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيِّنَاتٍ",
        "answer": "and clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "wabayyinātin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيِّنَاتُ",
        "answer": "(from) the clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "l-bayinātu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "209"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيِّنَاتُ",
        "answer": "the clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "l-bayinātu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "the clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "l-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيِّنَاتُ",
        "answer": "the clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "332",
        "tlit": "l-bayinātu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَاتٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "bayyinātin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَةٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "bayyinatin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "475",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "open",
        "pcklId": "476",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبِعَ",
        "answer": "follows",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tabiʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبِعُوا",
        "answer": "they would follow",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتْبَعُهَا",
        "answer": "followed [it]",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yatbaʿuhā",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتْبِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they follow",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yut'biʿūna",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّبَعُوا",
        "answer": "And they followed",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wa-ittabaʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعَ",
        "answer": "you follow",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعْتَ",
        "answer": "you follow",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿta",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّبِعُ",
        "answer": "follows",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yattabiʿu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعْتَ",
        "answer": "you followed",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿta",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتُّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "were followed",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ittubiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعُوا",
        "answer": "followed",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعُوا",
        "answer": "followed",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "Follow",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ittabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتَّبِعُ",
        "answer": "we follow",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "nattabiʿu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِتَابِعٍ",
        "answer": "a follower",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "bitābiʿin",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِتَابِعٍ",
        "answer": "(are) followers",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "bitābiʿin",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتِّبَاعٌ",
        "answer": "then follows up",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "fa-ittibāʿun",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "تِجَارَتُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their commerce",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tijāratuhum",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تِجَارَةً",
        "answer": "a transaction",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tijāratan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "under them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) dust",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "turābun",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَكَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and left them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "watarakahum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَكَ",
        "answer": "he leaves",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taraka",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَكَ",
        "answer": "(was) left",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taraka",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرَكَهُ",
        "answer": "then left it",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fatarakahu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتْلُونَ",
        "answer": "[you] recite",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tatlūna",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتْلُو",
        "answer": "recite(d)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tatlū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتْلُونَ",
        "answer": "recite",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yatlūna",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتْلُونَهُ",
        "answer": "recite it",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yatlūnahu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتْلُو",
        "answer": "(who) will recite",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yatlū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتْلُو",
        "answer": "(who) recites",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yatlū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتْلُوهَا",
        "answer": "We recite them",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "natlūhā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "252"
    },
    {
        "question": "تِلَاوَتِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) its recitation",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "tilāwatihi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَتَمَّهُنَّ",
        "answer": "and he fulfilled them",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fa-atammahunna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِأُتِمَّ",
        "answer": "And that I complete",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wali-utimma",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتِمُّوا",
        "answer": "complete",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "atimmū",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَتِمُّوا",
        "answer": "And complete",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-atimmū",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتِمَّ",
        "answer": "complete",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yutimma",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَابَ",
        "answer": "So (his Lord) turned",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fatāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتُوبُوا",
        "answer": "So turn in repentance",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fatūbū",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَابَ",
        "answer": "Then He turned",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fatāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُبْ",
        "answer": "and turn",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "watub",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابُوا",
        "answer": "who repent[ed]",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tābū",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتُوبُ",
        "answer": "I will accept repentance",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "atūbu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَابَ",
        "answer": "so He turned",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fatāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you repent",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tub'tum",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّوَّابُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Oft-returning (to mercy)",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "l-tawābu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّوَّابُ",
        "answer": "(is) the-returning",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-tawābu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّوَّابُ",
        "answer": "the Oft-returning",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "l-tawābu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّوَّابُ",
        "answer": "the Acceptor of Repentance",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "l-tawābu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّوَّابِينَ",
        "answer": "those who turn in repentance",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-tawābīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَثَبِّتْ",
        "answer": "and make firm",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wathabbit",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَثْبِيتًا",
        "answer": "and certainty",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "watathbītan",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَقِفْتُمُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you find them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "thaqif'tumūhum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَلَاثَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) three",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "thalāthati",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَلَاثَةَ",
        "answer": "(for) three",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "thalāthata",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "الثَّمَرَاتِ",
        "answer": "the fruits",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-thamarāti",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الثَّمَرَاتِ",
        "answer": "fruits",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-thamarāti",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالثَّمَرَاتِ",
        "answer": "and [the] fruits",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wal-thamarāti",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "الثَّمَرَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] fruits",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-thamarāti",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَرَةٍ",
        "answer": "fruit",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "thamaratin",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَنًا",
        "answer": "a price",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "thamanan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَنًا",
        "answer": "(for) a price",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "thamanan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَنًا",
        "answer": "a gain",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "thamanan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَتَا",
        "answer": "(of)",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ith'natā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَابَةً",
        "answer": "a place of return",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "mathābatan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَثُوبَةٌ",
        "answer": "surely (the) reward",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "lamathūbatun",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُثِيرُ",
        "answer": "to plough",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tuthīru",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَبَلٍ",
        "answer": "hill",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jabalin",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the blazing Fire",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِدَالَ",
        "answer": "quarrelling",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "jidāla",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "sail",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flowing",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُزْءًا",
        "answer": "a portion",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "juz'an",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْزِي",
        "answer": "avail",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tajzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْزِي",
        "answer": "will avail",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tajzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(should be the) recompense",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(is the) reward",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجِسْمِ",
        "answer": "and [the] physique",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-jis'mi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "They put",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yajʿalūna",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "made",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْعَلُوا",
        "answer": "set up",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tajʿalū",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَجْعَلُ",
        "answer": "Will You place",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "atajʿalu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "So We made it",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fajaʿalnāhā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We made",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "اجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "make",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ij'ʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاجْعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "[and] Make us",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-ij'ʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We made you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnākum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We made",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْعَلُوا",
        "answer": "make",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "tajʿalū",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِنَجْعَلَكَ",
        "answer": "and We will make you",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "walinajʿalaka",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "اجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "put",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ij'ʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاعِلٌ",
        "answer": "going to place",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "jāʿilun",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاعِلُكَ",
        "answer": "(am) the One to make you",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "jāʿiluka",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْمَعِينَ",
        "answer": "all together",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ajmaʿīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all (of you)",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "together",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحَ",
        "answer": "blame",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "junāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحٌ",
        "answer": "any sin",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "junāḥun",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحَ",
        "answer": "sin",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "junāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحَ",
        "answer": "sin",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "junāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحَ",
        "answer": "blame",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "junāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحَ",
        "answer": "blame",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "junāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحَ",
        "answer": "blame",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "junāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحَ",
        "answer": "blame",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "junāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحَ",
        "answer": "blame",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "junāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحَ",
        "answer": "blame",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "junāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحٌ",
        "answer": "any sin",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "junāḥun",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْجُنُودِ",
        "answer": "with the forces",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bil-junūdi",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجُنُودِهِ",
        "answer": "and his troops",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wajunūdihi",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجُنُودِهِ",
        "answer": "and his troops",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wajunūdihi",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَفًا",
        "answer": "(any) error",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "janafan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "(will be) Gardens",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّةٍ",
        "answer": "a garden",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "jannatin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّةٌ",
        "answer": "a garden",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "jannatun",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "(in) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "the Paradise",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاهَدُوا",
        "answer": "and strove",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wajāhadū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَهْرَةً",
        "answer": "manifestly",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "jahratan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَاهِلِينَ",
        "answer": "the ignorant",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-jāhilīna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَاهِلُ",
        "answer": "the ignorant one",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-jāhilu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُجِيبُ",
        "answer": "I respond",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ujību",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَسْتَجِيبُوا",
        "answer": "So let them respond",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "falyastajībū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاوَزَهُ",
        "answer": "he crossed it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jāwazahu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجُوعِ",
        "answer": "and [the] hunger",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-jūʿi",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْتَ",
        "answer": "you have come",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ji'ta",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "came to you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "came to you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكَ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "jāaka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكَ",
        "answer": "came to you",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "jāaka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْكُمُ",
        "answer": "came to you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "jāatkumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "209"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُ",
        "answer": "it (has) come to him ",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "jāathu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "jāathumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "jāathumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُ",
        "answer": "comes to him",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "jāahu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّونَهُمْ",
        "answer": "They love them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbūnahum",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "like",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "loves",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحِبُّوا",
        "answer": "you love",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tuḥibbū",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "loves",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "and loves",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wayuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَحُبِّ",
        "answer": "as (they should) love",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "kaḥubbi",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُبًّا",
        "answer": "(in) love",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "ḥubban",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُبِّهِ",
        "answer": "spite of his love (for it)",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "ḥubbihi",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبَّةٍ",
        "answer": "a grain",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "ḥabbatin",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبَّةٍ",
        "answer": "grain(s)",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "ḥabbatin",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبِطَتْ",
        "answer": "became worthless",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥabiṭat",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَجَّ",
        "answer": "performs Hajj",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥajja",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُحَاجُّوكُمْ",
        "answer": "so that they argue with you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "liyuḥājjūkum",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتُحَاجُّونَنَا",
        "answer": "Do you argue with us",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "atuḥājjūnanā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاجَّ",
        "answer": "argued",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥājja",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحَجِّ",
        "answer": "and (for) the Hajj",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥaji",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَجَّ",
        "answer": "the Hajj",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaja",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَجِّ",
        "answer": "(by) the Hajj",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaji",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَجِّ",
        "answer": "the Hajj",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaji",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَجُّ",
        "answer": "(For) the Hajj",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "al-ḥaju",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَجَّ",
        "answer": "the Hajj",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaja",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَجِّ",
        "answer": "the Hajj",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaji",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُجَّةٌ",
        "answer": "any argument",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ḥujjatun",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحِجَارَةُ",
        "answer": "and [the] stones",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥijāratu",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالْحِجَارَةِ",
        "answer": "(became) like [the] stones",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kal-ḥijārati",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحِجَارَةِ",
        "answer": "the stones",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-ḥijārati",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَجَرَ",
        "answer": "the stone",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-ḥajara",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتُحَدِّثُونَهُمْ",
        "answer": "Do you tell them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "atuḥaddithūnahum",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُدُودُ",
        "answer": "(are the) limits",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥudūdu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُدُودَ",
        "answer": "(the) limits",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḥudūda",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُدُودَ",
        "answer": "(the) limits",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥudūda",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُدُودُ",
        "answer": "(are the) limits",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ḥudūdu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُدُودَ",
        "answer": "(the) limits",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ḥudūda",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُدُودَ",
        "answer": "(the) limits",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ḥudūda",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُدُودُ",
        "answer": "(are the) limits",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḥudūdu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاحْذَرُوهُ",
        "answer": "so beware of Him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-iḥ'dharūhu",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَذَرَ",
        "answer": "(in) fear (of)",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ḥadhara",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَذَرَ",
        "answer": "(in) fear",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ḥadhara",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَرْبٍ",
        "answer": "of a war",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "biḥarbin",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرْثَ",
        "answer": "the field",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ḥartha",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرْثَ",
        "answer": "the crops",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-ḥartha",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرْثٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a tilth",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥarthun",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرْثَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(to) your tilth",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥarthakum",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُرُّ",
        "answer": "the freeman",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ḥuru",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحُرِّ",
        "answer": "for the freeman",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥuri",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْرَصَ",
        "answer": "(the) most greedy",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aḥraṣa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَرِّفُونَهُ",
        "answer": "they distort it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuḥarrifūnahu",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاحْتَرَقَتْ",
        "answer": "then it is burnt",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fa-iḥ'taraqat",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "He has forbidden",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "but (has) forbidden",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامُ",
        "answer": "[the] sacred",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmu",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "[the] sacred",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "[the] Sacred",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "[the] sacred ",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحُرُمَاتُ",
        "answer": "and for all the violations",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥurumātu",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحَرَّمٌ",
        "answer": "(was) forbidden",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "muḥarramun",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) grieve",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسِبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "(do) you think",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥasib'tum",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْسَبُهُمُ",
        "answer": "Think (about) them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaḥsabuhumu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَاسِبْكُمْ",
        "answer": "will call you to account",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yuḥāsib'kum",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَحَسْبُهُ",
        "answer": "Then enough for him",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "faḥasbuhu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحِسَابِ",
        "answer": "(in taking) account",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "l-ḥisābi",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "202"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابٍ",
        "answer": "measure",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "ḥisābin",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَدًا",
        "answer": "(out of) jealousy",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥasadan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَرَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(as) regrets",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥasarātin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحْسِنُوا",
        "answer": "And do good",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥsinū",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ḥasanan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُسْنًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "ḥus'nan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنَةً",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "ḥasanatan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنَةً",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "ḥasanatan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِحْسَانًا",
        "answer": "(be) good",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "iḥ'sānan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِحْسَانٍ",
        "answer": "with kindness",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "bi-iḥ'sānin",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِحْسَانٍ",
        "answer": "with kindness",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "bi-iḥ'sānin",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers (in reward)",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحْسِنٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a good-doer",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "muḥ'sinun",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحْشَرُونَ",
        "answer": "will be gathered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tuḥ'sharūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحْصِرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are held back",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "uḥ'ṣir'tum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحْصِرُوا",
        "answer": "are wrapped up",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "uḥ'ṣirū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَضَرَ",
        "answer": "came to",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥaḍara",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَضَرَ",
        "answer": "approaches",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥaḍara",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاضِرِي",
        "answer": "present",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḥāḍirī",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاضِرَةً",
        "answer": "present",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ḥāḍiratan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِطَّةٌ",
        "answer": "Repentance",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥiṭṭatun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَافِظُوا",
        "answer": "Guard strictly",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ḥāfiẓū",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "238"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِفْظُهُمَا",
        "answer": "(the) guarding of both of them",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḥif'ẓuhumā",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(have) better right",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "aḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(are) more entitled",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "aḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the truth",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقَّ",
        "answer": "the Truth",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقَّ",
        "answer": "the Truth",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "[the] right",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "with the truth",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the truth",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "with the truth",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّ",
        "answer": "(as it has the) right",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the truth",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقَّ",
        "answer": "the Truth",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "The Truth",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "al-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَلْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) surely the truth",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "lalḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "with [the] Truth",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقًّا",
        "answer": "a duty",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqan",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in [the] truth",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the Truth",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقًّا",
        "answer": "a duty",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqan",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقًّا",
        "answer": "a duty",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqan",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "241"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in [the] truth",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "252"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the right",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the right",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمُ",
        "answer": "will judge",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaḥkumu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَحْكُمَ",
        "answer": "to judge",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "liyaḥkuma",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحِكْمَةَ",
        "answer": "and the wisdom",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥik'mata",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحِكْمَةَ",
        "answer": "and the wisdom",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥik'mata",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحِكْمَةِ",
        "answer": "and [the] wisdom",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥik'mati",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحِكْمَةَ",
        "answer": "and the wisdom",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥik'mata",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحِكْمَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] wisdom",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-ḥik'mata",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحِكْمَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] wisdom",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-ḥik'mata",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "209"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُكَّامِ",
        "answer": "the authorities",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "l-ḥukāmi",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْلِقُوا",
        "answer": "shave",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taḥliqū",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحِلُّ",
        "answer": "lawful",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaḥillu",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحِلُّ",
        "answer": "lawful",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaḥillu",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحِلُّ",
        "answer": "lawful",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taḥillu",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحِلَّ",
        "answer": "Permitted",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "uḥilla",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحَلَّ",
        "answer": "While has permitted",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥalla",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلَالًا",
        "answer": "lawful",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ḥalālan",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحِلَّهُ",
        "answer": "(to) its destination",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "maḥillahu",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Forbearing",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥalīmun",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Forbearing",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ḥalīmun",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Forbearing",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ḥalīmun",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَمْدِكَ",
        "answer": "with Your praises",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "biḥamdika",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمِيدٌ",
        "answer": "Praiseworthy",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ḥamīdun",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِمَارِكَ",
        "answer": "your donkey",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥimārika",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْمِلُهُ",
        "answer": "will carry it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taḥmiluhu",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْمِلْ",
        "answer": "lay",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taḥmil",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمَلْتَهُ",
        "answer": "(which) You laid [it]",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥamaltahu",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحَمِّلْنَا",
        "answer": "lay on us",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "tuḥammil'nā",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَنِيفًا",
        "answer": "(the) upright",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥanīfan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحَاطَتْ",
        "answer": "and surrounded him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥāṭat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِيطُونَ",
        "answer": "they encompass",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuḥīṭūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحِيطٌ",
        "answer": "(is) [the One Who] encompasses",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "muḥīṭun",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَوْلِ",
        "answer": "the year",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-ḥawli",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَوْلَهُ",
        "answer": "(was) around him",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ḥawlahu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَوْلَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(for) two years",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ḥawlayni",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "where",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "(from) wherever",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَيْثُ",
        "answer": "and wherever",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "waḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَيْثُ",
        "answer": "And wherever",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "waḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَحِيضِ",
        "answer": "[the] menstruation",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-maḥīḍi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَحِيضِ",
        "answer": "(their) [the] menstruation",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-maḥīḍi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينٍ",
        "answer": "a period",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥīnin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحِينَ",
        "answer": "and (the) time",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "waḥīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَحْيَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "then He gave you life",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fa-aḥyākum",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will give you life",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yīkum",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِي",
        "answer": "revives",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَحْيَا",
        "answer": "giving life",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fa-aḥyā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْيَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "He restored them to life",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "aḥyāhum",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِي",
        "answer": "grants life",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحْيِي",
        "answer": "give life",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "uḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِي",
        "answer": "(will) bring to life",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحْيِي",
        "answer": "You give life",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "tuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَحْيِي",
        "answer": "ashamed",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "yastaḥyī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَحْيُونَ",
        "answer": "and letting live",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wayastaḥyūna",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْيَاءٌ",
        "answer": "(they are) alive",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "aḥyāon",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيُّ",
        "answer": "the Ever-Living",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةَ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayata",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيَاةٍ",
        "answer": "life",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "ḥayatin",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيَاةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) life",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "ḥayatun",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةُ",
        "answer": "(is) the life",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayatu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَبِيثَ",
        "answer": "the bad",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-khabītha",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "khabīrun",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "khabīrun",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَخَبَّطُهُ",
        "answer": "confounds him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yatakhabbaṭuhu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَتَمَ",
        "answer": "Has set a seal",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khatama",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْدَعُونَ",
        "answer": "they deceive",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yakhdaʿūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخَادِعُونَ",
        "answer": "They seek to deceive",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yukhādiʿūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَرَابِهَا",
        "answer": "their destruction",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kharābihā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَخْرُجُ",
        "answer": "so comes out",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fayakhruju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَرَجْتَ",
        "answer": "you start forth",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kharajta",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَرَجْتَ",
        "answer": "you start forth",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kharajta",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَرَجْنَ",
        "answer": "they leave",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kharajna",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَرَجُوا",
        "answer": "went out",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kharajū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخْرَجَ",
        "answer": "then brought forth",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "fa-akhraja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخْرَجَهُمَا",
        "answer": "and he got [both of] them out",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "fa-akhrajahumā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْرِجْ",
        "answer": "to bring forth",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "yukh'rij",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُخْرِجُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) evict",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "tukh'rijūna",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُخْرِجُونَ",
        "answer": "and evict",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "watukh'rijūna",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخْرِجُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "and drive them out",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wa-akhrijūhum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرَجُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they drove you out",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "akhrajūkum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرِجْنَا",
        "answer": "we have been driven",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ukh'rij'nā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْرِجُهُمْ",
        "answer": "He brings them out",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "yukh'rijuhum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْرِجُونَهُمْ",
        "answer": "they bring them out",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "yukh'rijūnahum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرَجْنَا",
        "answer": "We brought forth",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "akhrajnā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَارِجِينَ",
        "answer": "will come out",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "bikhārijīna",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِخْرَاجُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their eviction",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "ikh'rājuhum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِخْرَاجُ",
        "answer": "and driving out",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'rāju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِخْرَاجٍ",
        "answer": "driving (them) out",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "ikh'rājin",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْرِجٌ",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who brought forth",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "mukh'rijun",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِزْيٌ",
        "answer": "disgrace",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "khiz'yun",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِزْيٌ",
        "answer": "(is) disgrace",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "khiz'yun",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاسِئِينَ",
        "answer": "despised",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khāsiīna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the losers",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirūna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the losers",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirūna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاشِعِينَ",
        "answer": "the humble ones",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-khāshiʿīna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْشَوْهُمْ",
        "answer": "fear them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "takhshawhum",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاخْشَوْنِي",
        "answer": "but fear Me",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'shawnī",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَشْيَةِ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "khashyati",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْتَصُّ",
        "answer": "chooses",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yakhtaṣṣu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخِصَامِ",
        "answer": "(of) opponents",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-khiṣāmi",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْطَأْنَا",
        "answer": "we err",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "akhṭanā",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَطَايَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "your sins",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "khaṭāyākum",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَطِيئَتُهُ",
        "answer": "his sins ",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "khaṭīatuhu",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِطْبَةِ",
        "answer": "marriage proposal",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "khiṭ'bati",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْطَفُ",
        "answer": "snatches away",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yakhṭafu",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُطُوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) footsteps (of)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khuṭuwāti",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُطُوَاتِ",
        "answer": "footsteps",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khuṭuwāti",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخَفَّفُ",
        "answer": "will be lightened",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yukhaffafu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخَفَّفُ",
        "answer": "will be lightened",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yukhaffafu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْفِيفٌ",
        "answer": "a concession",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "takhfīfun",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُخْفُوهَا",
        "answer": "you keep it secret",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tukh'fūhā",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُخْفُوهُ",
        "answer": "you conceal it",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tukh'fūhu",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(Will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِصَةً",
        "answer": "exclusively",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "khāliṣatan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْلِصُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) sincere",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "mukh'liṣūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُخَالِطُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you associate with them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tukhāliṭūhum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْلِفَ",
        "answer": "will break",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yukh'lifa",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْتَلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "differing",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yakhtalifūna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْتَلَفُوا",
        "answer": "who differed",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ikh'talafū",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْتَلَفُوا",
        "answer": "they differed",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ikh'talafū",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْتَلَفَ",
        "answer": "differ[ed]",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ikh'talafa",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْتَلَفُوا",
        "answer": "they differed",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ikh'talafū",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْتَلَفُوا",
        "answer": "they differed",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ikh'talafū",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفَهَا",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "khalfahā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) behind them",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "khalfahum",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلِيفَةً",
        "answer": "a vicegerent",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "khalīfatan",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاخْتِلَافِ",
        "answer": "and alternation",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'tilāfi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "created you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khalaqakum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "(has been) created",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَاقٍ",
        "answer": "share",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "khalāqin",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَاقٍ",
        "answer": "any share",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "khalāqin",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقِ",
        "answer": "(the) creation",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "khalqi",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلَّةٌ",
        "answer": "friendship",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "khullatun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَوْا",
        "answer": "they are alone",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khalaw",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَا",
        "answer": "meet in private",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khalā",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَتْ",
        "answer": "has passed away",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khalat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَتْ",
        "answer": "has passed away",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khalat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَوْا",
        "answer": "passed away",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "khalaw",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَمْرِ",
        "answer": "[the] intoxicants",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-khamri",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخِنْزِيرِ",
        "answer": "(of) swine",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-khinzīri",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَافَ",
        "answer": "fears",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khāfa",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخَافَا",
        "answer": "both fear",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yakhāfā",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you fear",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khif'tum",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you fear",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khif'tum",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَوْفِ",
        "answer": "[the] fear",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-khawfi",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَائِفِينَ",
        "answer": "(like) those in fear",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "khāifīna",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْتَانُونَ",
        "answer": "deceive",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "takhtānūna",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاوِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "(had) overturned",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khāwiyatun",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(would have been) better",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "better",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bikhayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good (deeds)",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "khayran",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "khayran",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "khayran",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرَ",
        "answer": "(the) best",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "khayra",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) good",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) best",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(are) better",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "khayran",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(it is) better",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَيْرَاتِ",
        "answer": "(to) the good",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "l-khayrāti",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَيْطُ",
        "answer": "the thread",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-khayṭu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَيْطِ",
        "answer": "the thread",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-khayṭi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَابَّةٍ",
        "answer": "moving creature",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "dābbatin",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "Enter",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ud'khulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَادْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "and enter",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-ud'khulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْخُلَ",
        "answer": "will enter",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yadkhula",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْخُلُوهَا",
        "answer": "they enter them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yadkhulūhā",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "Enter",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ud'khulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "you will enter",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tadkhulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَادَّارَأْتُمْ",
        "answer": "then you disputed",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fa-iddāratum",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَجَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a degree",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "darajatun",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَجَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(in) degrees",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "darajātin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَادْعُوا",
        "answer": "and call",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-id'ʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَادْعُ",
        "answer": "so pray",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-ud'ʿu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُ",
        "answer": "Pray",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ud'ʿu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُ",
        "answer": "Pray",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ud'ʿu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُ",
        "answer": "Pray",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ud'ʿu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعَانِ",
        "answer": "he calls Me",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "daʿāni",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "they invite",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُو",
        "answer": "invites",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yadʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُهُنَّ",
        "answer": "call them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ud'ʿuhunna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُعُوا",
        "answer": "they are called",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "duʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُعَاءً",
        "answer": "calls",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "duʿāan",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعْوَةَ",
        "answer": "(to the) invocation",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "daʿwata",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّاعِ",
        "answer": "(of) the supplicant",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "l-dāʿi",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَفْعُ",
        "answer": "(for the) repelling",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "dafʿu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُدْلُوا",
        "answer": "and present",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "watud'lū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "[the] blood[s]",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-dimāa",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِمَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your blood",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "dimāakum",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالدَّمَ",
        "answer": "and [the] blood",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-dama",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) inferior",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "adnā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَدْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "and nearer",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-adnā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُدِيرُونَهَا",
        "answer": "you carry out",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tudīrūnahā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِيَارِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your homes",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "diyārikum",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِيَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their homes",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "diyārihim",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّارُ",
        "answer": "the home",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-dāru",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِيَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their homes",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "diyārihim",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِيَارِنَا",
        "answer": "our homes",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "diyārinā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "excluding",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدَايَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you contract with one another",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tadāyantum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينَ",
        "answer": "the religion",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-dīna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينُ",
        "answer": "the religion",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-dīnu",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your religion",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "dīnikum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينِهِ",
        "answer": "his religion",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "dīnihi",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "the religion",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِدَيْنٍ",
        "answer": "any debt",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "bidaynin",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذْبَحُوا",
        "answer": "you slaughter",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tadhbaḥū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَذَبَحُوهَا",
        "answer": "So they slaughtered it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fadhabaḥūhā",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُذَبِّحُونَ",
        "answer": "slaughtering",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yudhabbiḥūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتِي",
        "answer": "my offspring",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatī",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتِنَا",
        "answer": "our offspring",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatinā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّةٌ",
        "answer": "children",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatun",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "Remember",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "Remember",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "and remember",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُذْكَرَ",
        "answer": "be mentioned",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yudh'kara",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "Remember",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاذْكُرُونِي",
        "answer": "So remember Me",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fa-udh'kurūnī",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذْكُرْكُمْ",
        "answer": "I will remember you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "adhkur'kum",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "then remember",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوهُ",
        "answer": "And remember Him",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurūhu",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "then remember",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "And remember",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "and remember",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَتَذْكُرُونَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "will mention them",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "satadhkurūnahunna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "then remember",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "fa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتُذَكِّرَ",
        "answer": "then will remind",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "fatudhakkira",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "take heed",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "yatadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذَّكَّرُ",
        "answer": "remembers",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "yadhakkaru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِكْرِكُمْ",
        "answer": "as you remember",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "kadhik'rikum",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرًا",
        "answer": "remembrance",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "dhik'ran",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَلُولٌ",
        "answer": "trained",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "dhalūlun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذِّلَّةُ",
        "answer": "the humiliation",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-dhilatu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَهَبَ",
        "answer": "took away",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "dhahaba",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَذَهَبَ",
        "answer": "He would certainly have taken away",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ladhahaba",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُءُوسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your heads",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ruūsakum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأْسِهِ",
        "answer": "his head",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "rasihi",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُءُوسُ",
        "answer": "(is)",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ruūsu",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَرَءُوفٌ",
        "answer": "Full of Kindness",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "laraūfun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَءُوفٌ",
        "answer": "(is) full of Kindness",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "raūfun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "207"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَرَى",
        "answer": "we see",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "narā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "We see",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "narā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَى",
        "answer": "would see",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْنَ",
        "answer": "they will see",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yarawna",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَأَوُا",
        "answer": "and they will see",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wara-awū",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُرِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "and shows you",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "wayurīkum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرِنَا",
        "answer": "And show us",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "wa-arinā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيهِمُ",
        "answer": "will show them",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "yurīhimu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرِنِي",
        "answer": "show me",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "arinī",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِئَاءَ",
        "answer": "(to) be seen",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "riāa",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكُمُ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "rabbakumu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "(to) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "(to) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "(to) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "(to) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "rabbuhu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "(saying), \"Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "rabbuhu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّ",
        "answer": "to (the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "lirabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "(is) our Lord",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your Lord",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "warabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّيَ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "rabbiya",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "His Lord",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِحَتْ",
        "answer": "profited",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "rabiḥat",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَرَبَّصْنَ",
        "answer": "shall wait",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yatarabbaṣna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَرَبَّصْنَ",
        "answer": "(the widows) should wait",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yatarabbaṣna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَبُّصُ",
        "answer": "(is a) waiting (of)",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tarabbuṣu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَعِينَ",
        "answer": "forty",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "arbaʿīna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَعَةِ",
        "answer": "four",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "arbaʿati",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَعَةَ",
        "answer": "(for) four",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "arbaʿata",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَعَةً",
        "answer": "four",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "arbaʿatan",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُرْبِي",
        "answer": "and (gives) increase",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wayur'bī",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّبَا",
        "answer": "[the] usury",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-riba",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّبَا",
        "answer": "[the] usury",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-riba",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّبَا",
        "answer": "[the] usury",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-riba",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّبَا",
        "answer": "the usury",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-riba",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّبَا",
        "answer": "[the] usury",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-riba",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "278"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبْوَةٍ",
        "answer": "on a height",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "birabwatin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجْزًا",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "rij'zan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "[they] will not return",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجَعْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you return",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "rajaʿtum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُ",
        "answer": "return",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿu",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be brought back",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَرَاجَعَا",
        "answer": "they return to each other",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "yatarājaʿā",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "will return",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "rājiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "will return",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "rājiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلرِّجَالِ",
        "answer": "and for the men",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "walilrrijāli",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِجَالًا",
        "answer": "then (pray) on foot",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "farijālan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجَالِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your men",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "rijālikum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two men",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "rajulayni",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَجُلٌ",
        "answer": "then one man",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "farajulun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجُونَ",
        "answer": "they hope",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yarjūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْحَمْنَا",
        "answer": "and have mercy on us",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ir'ḥamnā",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْحَامِهِنَّ",
        "answer": "their wombs",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "arḥāmihinna",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَتُهُ",
        "answer": "and His Mercy",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatuhu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَحْمَتِهِ",
        "answer": "for His Mercy",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "biraḥmatihi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةٌ",
        "answer": "and Mercy",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةٌ",
        "answer": "and mercy",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتَ",
        "answer": "(for) Mercy",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "raḥmata",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Merciful",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "192"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرَدُّونَ",
        "answer": "they will be sent back",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuraddūna",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرُدُّونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "they could turn you back",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaruddūnakum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرُدُّوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they turn you away",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaruddūkum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْتَدِدْ",
        "answer": "turns away",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yartadid",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَدِّهِنَّ",
        "answer": "to take them back",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "biraddihinna",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We have provided them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "razaqnāhum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُزِقُوا",
        "answer": "they are provided",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ruziqū",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُزِقْنَا",
        "answer": "we were provided",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ruziq'nā",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We have provided you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "razaqnākum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْزُقْ",
        "answer": "and provide",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-ur'zuq",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We have provided you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "razaqnākum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْزُقُ",
        "answer": "provides",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yarzuqu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We (have) provided you",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "razaqnākum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقًا",
        "answer": "(as) provision",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "riz'qan",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقًا",
        "answer": "(as) provision",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "riz'qan",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقِ",
        "answer": "(the) provision (of)",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "riz'qi",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقُهُنَّ",
        "answer": "(is) their provision",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "riz'quhunna",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "[We] have sent you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "arsalnāka",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالرُّسُلِ",
        "answer": "with [the] Messengers",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "bil-rusuli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٌ",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "rasūlun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرُسُلِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messengers",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "warusulihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٌ",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "rasūlun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Messenger",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "rasūlakum",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "l-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولَ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-rasūla",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "l-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّسُلُ",
        "answer": "(are) the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "l-rusulu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "l-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرُسُلِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messengers",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "warusulihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلِهِ",
        "answer": "His messengers",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "rusulihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "477",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "252"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْشُدُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) led aright",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yarshudūna",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّشْدُ",
        "answer": "the right (path)",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-rush'du",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرْضِعْنَ",
        "answer": "shall suckle",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yur'ḍiʿ'na",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَرْضِعُوا",
        "answer": "ask another women to suckle",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tastarḍiʿū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّضَاعَةَ",
        "answer": "the suckling",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-raḍāʿata",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "will be pleased",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tarḍā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْضَاهَا",
        "answer": "you will be pleased with",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tarḍāhā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْضَوْنَ",
        "answer": "you agree",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tarḍawna",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَاضَوْا",
        "answer": "they agree",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "tarāḍaw",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْضَاتِ",
        "answer": "pleasure",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "marḍāti",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "207"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْضَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) pleasure",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "marḍāti",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَاضٍ",
        "answer": "mutual consent",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "tarāḍin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَعْدٌ",
        "answer": "and thunder",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waraʿdun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاعِنَا",
        "answer": "Raina",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "rāʿinā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْغَبُ",
        "answer": "will turn away",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yarghabu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَغَدًا",
        "answer": "freely",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "raghadan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَغَدًا",
        "answer": "abundantly",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "raghadan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّفَثُ",
        "answer": "(is) the approach",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-rafathu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَفَثَ",
        "answer": "sexual relations",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "rafatha",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَفَعْنَا",
        "answer": "and We raised",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "warafaʿnā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَفَعْنَا",
        "answer": "and We raised",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "warafaʿnā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْفَعُ",
        "answer": "(was) raising",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yarfaʿu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَفَعَ",
        "answer": "and He raised",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "warafaʿa",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّقَابِ",
        "answer": "freeing the necks (slaves)",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-riqābi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُكْبَانًا",
        "answer": "riding",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ruk'bānan",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْكَعُوا",
        "answer": "and bow down",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ir'kaʿū",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّاكِعِينَ",
        "answer": "those who bow down",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-rākiʿīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالرُّكَّعِ",
        "answer": "and those who bow down",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wal-rukaʿi",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَارْهَبُونِ",
        "answer": "fear [Me]",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-ir'habūni",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِهَانٌ",
        "answer": "then pledge",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "farihānun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرُوحِ",
        "answer": "(with)",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "birūḥi",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرُوحِ",
        "answer": "with Spirit",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "birūḥi",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّيَاحِ",
        "answer": "(of) the winds",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-riyāḥi",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "(did) intend",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) you wish",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "turīdūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "Intends",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "intends",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادُوا",
        "answer": "they wish",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "arādū",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "wishes",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَا",
        "answer": "they both desire",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "arādā",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَدْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you want",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "aradttum",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "He intends",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْتَابُوا",
        "answer": "you (have) doubt",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tartābū",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَيْبَ",
        "answer": "doubt",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "rayba",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَيْبٍ",
        "answer": "doubt",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "raybin",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمُزَحْزِحِهِ",
        "answer": "(will) remove him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bimuzaḥziḥihi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُزَكِّيهِمْ",
        "answer": "and purify them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wayuzakkīhim",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُزَكِّيكُمْ",
        "answer": "and purifies you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wayuzakkīkum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُزَكِّيهِمْ",
        "answer": "will He purify them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yuzakkīhim",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْكَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) more virtuous",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "azkā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "zakah",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "[the] zakah",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزُلْزِلُوا",
        "answer": "and they were shaken",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wazul'zilū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَلَلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you slip",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "zalaltum",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "209"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَزَلَّهُمَا",
        "answer": "Then made [both of] them slip",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fa-azallahumā",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجٌ",
        "answer": "spouses",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "azwājun",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَوْجُكَ",
        "answer": "and your spouse",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wazawjuka",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَوْجِهِ",
        "answer": "and his spouse",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wazawjihi",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَوْجًا",
        "answer": "a spouse",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "zawjan",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "their husbands",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "azwājahunna",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجًا",
        "answer": "wives",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "azwājan",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجًا",
        "answer": "(their) wives",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "azwājan",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَزْوَاجِهِمْ",
        "answer": "for their wives",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "li-azwājihim",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَزَوَّدُوا",
        "answer": "And take provision",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "watazawwadū",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّادِ",
        "answer": "provision",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-zādi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَزَادَهُمُ",
        "answer": "so has increased them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fazādahumu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَنَزِيدُ",
        "answer": "And We will increase",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wasanazīdu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَادَهُ",
        "answer": "and increased him",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wazādahu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزَالُونَ",
        "answer": "they will cease",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yazālūna",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُيِّنَ",
        "answer": "Beautified",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "zuyyina",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأَلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have asked (for)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sa-altum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْأَلُوا",
        "answer": "you ask",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tasalū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُئِلَ",
        "answer": "was asked",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "su-ila",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسْأَلُ",
        "answer": "you will be asked",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tus'alu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسْأَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be asked",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tus'alūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسْأَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be asked",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tus'alūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأَلَكَ",
        "answer": "ask you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "sa-alaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلْ",
        "answer": "Ask",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "sal",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "And they ask you",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wayasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wayasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "And they ask you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wayasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) they ask",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yasalūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّائِلِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who ask",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "wal-sāilīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْأَمُوا",
        "answer": "(be) weary",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tasamū",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْبَابُ",
        "answer": "the relations",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-asbābu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبْتِ",
        "answer": "the (matter of) Sabbath",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-sabti",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُسَبِّحُ",
        "answer": "[we] glorify (You)",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nusabbiḥu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَكَ",
        "answer": "Glory be to You",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānaka",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَهُ",
        "answer": "Glory be to Him",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānahu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَسْبَاطِ",
        "answer": "and the descendants",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-asbāṭi",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَسْبَاطَ",
        "answer": "and the descendants",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-asbāṭa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعَ",
        "answer": "seven",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sabʿa",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعَ",
        "answer": "seven",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sabʿa",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَبْعَةٍ",
        "answer": "and seven (days)",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wasabʿatin",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَبِقُوا",
        "answer": "so race",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tabiqū",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(of) the way",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "the wayfarer",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "the wayfarer",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "244"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْجُدُوا",
        "answer": "Prostrate",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "us'judū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَجَدُوا",
        "answer": "[so] they prostrated",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fasajadū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّجُودِ",
        "answer": "and those who prostrate",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-sujūdi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَاجِدَ",
        "answer": "(the) masajid",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "masājida",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "(of) Al-Masjid",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "(of) Al-Masjid",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "(of) Al-Masjid",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسَاجِدِ",
        "answer": "the masajid",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-masājidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "(near) Al-Masjid",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "and (preventing access to) Al-Masjid",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wal-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُجَّدًا",
        "answer": "prostrating",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "sujjadan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّحَابِ",
        "answer": "and the clouds",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-saḥābi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "السِّحْرَ",
        "answer": "[the] magic",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-siḥ'ra",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْخَرُونَ",
        "answer": "and they ridicule",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayaskharūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسَخَّرِ",
        "answer": "[the] controlled",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-musakhari",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَرِّحُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "release them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sarriḥūhunna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْرِيحٌ",
        "answer": "to release (her)",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tasrīḥun",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسُرُّ",
        "answer": "pleasing",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tasurru",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسِرُّونَ",
        "answer": "they conceal",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yusirrūna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِرًّا",
        "answer": "secretly",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "sirran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِرًّا",
        "answer": "secretly",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "sirran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَرِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) swift",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "sarīʿu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "202"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَعَىٰ",
        "answer": "and strives",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wasaʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعَىٰ",
        "answer": "he strives",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "saʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعْيًا",
        "answer": "(in) haste",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "saʿyan",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفَرٍ",
        "answer": "a journey",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "safarin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفَرٍ",
        "answer": "a journey",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "safarin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفَرٍ",
        "answer": "a journey",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "safarin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْفِكُ",
        "answer": "and will shed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayasfiku",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْفِكُونَ",
        "answer": "will you shed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tasfikūna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفِهَ",
        "answer": "fooled",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "safiha",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّفَهَاءُ",
        "answer": "the fools",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-sufahāu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّفَهَاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) the fools",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-sufahāu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّفَهَاءُ",
        "answer": "the foolish ones",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-sufahāu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفِيهًا",
        "answer": "(of) limited understanding",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "safīhan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْقِي",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tasqī",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَسْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "asked (for) water",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "is'tasqā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْكُنْ",
        "answer": "Dwell",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "us'kun",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَكِينَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) tranquility",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "sakīnatun",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَسْكَنَةُ",
        "answer": "and the misery",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "wal-maskanatu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَسَاكِينِ",
        "answer": "and the needy",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "wal-masākīni",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَسَاكِينَ",
        "answer": "and the needy",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wal-masākīna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِسْكِينٍ",
        "answer": "a poor",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "mis'kīnin",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَسَاكِينِ",
        "answer": "and the needy",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wal-masākīni",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَفَ",
        "answer": "(has) passed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "salafa",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَّمْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you pay",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sallamtum",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْلَمَ",
        "answer": "submits",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "aslama",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْلِمْ",
        "answer": "Submit (yourself)",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "aslim",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْلَمْتُ",
        "answer": "I (have) submitted (myself)",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "aslamtu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "السِّلْمِ",
        "answer": "Islam",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-sil'mi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَلَّمَةٌ",
        "answer": "sound",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "musallamatun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمَيْنِ",
        "answer": "both submissive",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "mus'limayni",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) submissive",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "mus'limūna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) submissive",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "mus'limūna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) submissive",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "mus'limūna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمَةً",
        "answer": "submissive",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "mus'limatan",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّلْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "and [the] quails",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-salwā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "(who used to) hear",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْمَعُوا",
        "answer": "and listen",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-is'maʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعْنَا",
        "answer": "We heard",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "samiʿ'nā",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْمَعُوا",
        "answer": "and listen",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-is'maʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُ",
        "answer": "(does) hear",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعَهُ",
        "answer": "he (has) heard [it]",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "samiʿahu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعْنَا",
        "answer": "We heard",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "samiʿ'nā",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمْعِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearing",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "samʿihim",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسَمْعِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearing",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "bisamʿihim",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "the All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "samīʿun",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "samīʿun",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "samīʿun",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "227"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "samīʿun",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "244"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "samīʿun",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the names ",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-asmāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَسْمَاءِ",
        "answer": "of (the) names",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bi-asmāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَسْمَائِهِمْ",
        "answer": "of their names",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "bi-asmāihim",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَسْمَائِهِمْ",
        "answer": "of their names",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "bi-asmāihim",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْمُهُ",
        "answer": "His name",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "us'muhu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "and the sky",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wal-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمَاوَاتٍ",
        "answer": "heavens",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "samāwātin",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(to) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَمًّى",
        "answer": "fixed",
        "pcklId": "376",
        "tlit": "musamman",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنَابِلَ",
        "answer": "ears",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "sanābila",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُنْبُلَةٍ",
        "answer": "ear",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "sunbulatin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَسَنَّهْ",
        "answer": "change with time",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yatasannah",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنَةٍ",
        "answer": "year(s)",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "sanatin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءَ",
        "answer": "horrible",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "sūa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسُّوءِ",
        "answer": "to (do) the evil",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "bil-sūi",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَةً",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "sayyi-atan",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَاتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your evil deeds",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "sayyiātikum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْوَدِ",
        "answer": "[the] black",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-aswadi",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسُورَةٍ",
        "answer": "a chapter",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bisūratin",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسُومُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(who were) afflicting you (with)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yasūmūnakum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسِيمَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "by their mark",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bisīmāhum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَوَّاهُنَّ",
        "answer": "and fashioned them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fasawwāhunna",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "He turned",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "is'tawā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءٌ",
        "answer": "(it) is same",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "sawāon",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءَ",
        "answer": "(the) evenness",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "sawāa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشَابَهَ",
        "answer": "look alike",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tashābaha",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشَابَهَتْ",
        "answer": "Became alike",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tashābahat",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَشَابِهًا",
        "answer": "(things) in resemblance",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mutashābihan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّجَرَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] tree",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-shajarata",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "stronger",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدِّ",
        "answer": "(the) most severe",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ashaddi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(are) stronger",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(is) worse",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدَّ",
        "answer": "(with) greater",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ashadda",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدُ",
        "answer": "(is) severe",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "shadīdu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدُ",
        "answer": "(is) severe",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "shadīdu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدُ",
        "answer": "(is) severe",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "shadīdu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاشْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "and drink",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ish'rabū",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاشْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "and drink",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-ish'rabū",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرِبَ",
        "answer": "drinks",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shariba",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَشَرِبُوا",
        "answer": "Then they drank",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fasharibū",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُشْرِبُوا",
        "answer": "And they were made to drink",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-ush'ribū",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَشَرَابِكَ",
        "answer": "and your drink",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "washarābika",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَشْرَبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their drinking place",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "mashrabahum",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) bad",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sharrun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْرِقُ",
        "answer": "(is) the east",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-mashriqu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْرِقُ",
        "answer": "(is) the east",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-mashriqu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْرِقِ",
        "answer": "the east",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-mashriqi",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْرِقِ",
        "answer": "the east",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-mashriqi",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكُوا",
        "answer": "associate[d] partners (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ashrakū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "those who associate partners (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "those who associated partners (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) [the] polytheistic men",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُشْرِكٍ",
        "answer": "a polytheistic man",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "mush'rikin",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] polytheistic women",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikāti",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُشْرِكَةٍ",
        "answer": "a polytheistic woman",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "mush'rikatin",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they sold",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sharaw",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْرِي",
        "answer": "sells",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yashrī",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "207"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَرَوُا",
        "answer": "bought",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ish'tarawū",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْتَرُوا",
        "answer": "exchange",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tashtarū",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَشْتَرُوا",
        "answer": "to barter",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "liyashtarū",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَرَوُا",
        "answer": "bought",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ish'tarawū",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَرَوْا",
        "answer": "(for) which they have sold",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ish'taraw",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَرَاهُ",
        "answer": "buys it",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ish'tarāhu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَشْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "and they purchase",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wayashtarūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَرَوُا",
        "answer": "purchase[d]",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ish'tarawū",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَطْرَ",
        "answer": "towards the direction",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shaṭra",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَطْرَهُ",
        "answer": "(in) its direction",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shaṭrahu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَطْرَ",
        "answer": "(in the) direction",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shaṭra",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَطْرَ",
        "answer": "(in the) direction",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "shaṭra",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَطْرَهُ",
        "answer": "(in) its direction",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "shaṭrahu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيَاطِينُ",
        "answer": "the devils",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-shayāṭīnu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيَاطِينَ",
        "answer": "the devils",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-shayāṭīna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانِ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "The Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "al-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيَاطِينِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their evil ones",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "shayāṭīnihim",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they realize (it)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they realize (it)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "perceive",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَعَائِرِ",
        "answer": "(the) symbols",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "shaʿāiri",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْعَرِ",
        "answer": "the Monument",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-mashʿari",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْفَعُ",
        "answer": "can intercede",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yashfaʿu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَفَاعَةٌ",
        "answer": "any intercession",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "shafāʿatun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَفَاعَةٌ",
        "answer": "any intercession",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "shafāʿatun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَفَاعَةٌ",
        "answer": "intercession",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "shafāʿatun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَّقَّقُ",
        "answer": "split",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yashaqqaqu",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِقَاقٍ",
        "answer": "dissension",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "shiqāqin",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِقَاقٍ",
        "answer": "schism",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "shiqāqin",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) grateful",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) grateful",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاشْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "and be grateful",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-ush'kurū",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاشْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "and be grateful",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-ush'kurū",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) grateful",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "grateful",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاكِرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Appreciative",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "shākirun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالشَّمْسِ",
        "answer": "the sun",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bil-shamsi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْهَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) witnessing",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tashhadūna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِدَ",
        "answer": "witnesses",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shahida",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُشْهِدُ",
        "answer": "and he calls to witness",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "wayush'hidu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَشْهِدُوا",
        "answer": "And take witness",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wa-ashhidū",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَشْهِدُوا",
        "answer": "And call for evidence",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wa-is'tashhidū",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهَادَةً",
        "answer": "a testimony",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "shahādatan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلشَّهَادَةِ",
        "answer": "for evidence",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "lilshahādati",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّهَادَةَ",
        "answer": "the evidence",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-shahādata",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُهَدَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your witnesses",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "shuhadāakum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُهَدَاءَ",
        "answer": "witnesses",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "shuhadāa",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُهَدَاءَ",
        "answer": "witnesses",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "shuhadāa",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدًا",
        "answer": "a witness",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "shahīdan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two witnesses",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "shahīdayni",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشُّهَدَاءِ",
        "answer": "[the] witnesses",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-shuhadāi",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشُّهَدَاءُ",
        "answer": "the witnesses",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-shuhadāu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدٌ",
        "answer": "(the) witness",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "shahīdun",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهْرُ",
        "answer": "Month",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shahru",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّهْرَ",
        "answer": "the month",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-shahra",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّهْرُ",
        "answer": "The month",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "al-shahru",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالشَّهْرِ",
        "answer": "(is) for the month",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bil-shahri",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْهُرٌ",
        "answer": "(are) months",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ashhurun",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّهْرِ",
        "answer": "the month",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-shahri",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْهُرٍ",
        "answer": "months",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ashhurin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْهُرٍ",
        "answer": "months",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ashhurin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَشَاوُرٍ",
        "answer": "and consultation",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "watashāwurin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "had willed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْتُمَا",
        "answer": "you [both] wish",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shi'tumā",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you wish[ed]",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shi'tum",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(had) willed",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you wish",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "shi'tum",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He willed",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(had) willed",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(had) willed",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "He willed",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِشَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "with something",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "bishayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٌ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "shayon",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "a thing",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "a thing",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِشَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "bishayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصَّابِئِينَ",
        "answer": "and the Sabians ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-ṣābiīna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْبِرَ",
        "answer": "we endure",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "naṣbira",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْبَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their endurance",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "aṣbarahum",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالصَّبْرِ",
        "answer": "through patience",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "bil-ṣabri",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالصَّبْرِ",
        "answer": "through patience",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "bil-ṣabri",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبْرًا",
        "answer": "patience",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "ṣabran",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the patient ones",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-ṣābirīna",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) the patient ones",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-ṣābirīna",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصَّابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who are patient",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "wal-ṣābirīna",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the patient ones",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-ṣābirīna",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصَابِعَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their fingers",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aṣābiʿahum",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِبْغَةَ",
        "answer": "(The) color (religion)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṣib'ghata",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِبْغَةً",
        "answer": "at coloring",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣib'ghatan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are) companions",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَدٌّ",
        "answer": "but hindering (people)",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "waṣaddun",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقُوا",
        "answer": "are true",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqū",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصَدَّقُوا",
        "answer": "you remit as charity",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "taṣaddaqū",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقَاتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your charities",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqātikum",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّدَقَاتِ",
        "answer": "the charities",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-ṣadaqāti",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّدَقَاتِ",
        "answer": "(for) the charities",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-ṣadaqāti",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقَةٍ",
        "answer": "charity",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqatin",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقَةٍ",
        "answer": "a charity",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqatin",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "[those who are] truthful",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَدِّقًا",
        "answer": "confirming",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "muṣaddiqan",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَدِّقًا",
        "answer": "confirming",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "muṣaddiqan",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَدِّقًا",
        "answer": "confirming",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "muṣaddiqan",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَدِّقٌ",
        "answer": "confirming",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "muṣaddiqun",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَدِّقٌ",
        "answer": "confirming",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "muṣaddiqun",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "a path",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "a path",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَصْرِيفِ",
        "answer": "and directing",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wataṣrīfi",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّوَاعِقِ",
        "answer": "the thunderclaps",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-ṣawāʿiqi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّاعِقَةُ",
        "answer": "the thunderbolt",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāʿiqatu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَغِيرًا",
        "answer": "small",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ṣaghīran",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاصْفَحُوا",
        "answer": "and overlook",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-iṣ'faḥū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَفْرَاءُ",
        "answer": "yellow",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṣafrāu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "اصْطَفَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We chose him",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "iṣ'ṭafaynāhu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "اصْطَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "has chosen",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "iṣ'ṭafā",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "اصْطَفَاهُ",
        "answer": "has chosen him",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "iṣ'ṭafāhu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَفْوَانٍ",
        "answer": "(that of a) smooth rock",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ṣafwānin",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْلَحُوا",
        "answer": "and reform[ed]",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣlaḥū",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْلَحَ",
        "answer": "then reconciles",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣlaḥa",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُصْلِحُوا",
        "answer": "and make peace",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "watuṣ'liḥū",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "good deeds",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِصْلَاحٌ",
        "answer": "Setting right (their affairs)",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "iṣ'lāḥun",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِصْلَاحًا",
        "answer": "(for) reconciliation",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "iṣ'lāḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) reformers",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "muṣ'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُصْلِحِ",
        "answer": "the amender",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "l-muṣ'liḥi",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَلْدًا",
        "answer": "bare",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ṣaldan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصَّلَاةِ",
        "answer": "and the prayer",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-ṣalati",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصَّلَاةِ",
        "answer": "and the prayer",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wal-ṣalati",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَلَوَاتٌ",
        "answer": "(are) blessings",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ṣalawātun",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the prayers",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalawāti",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "238"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصَّلَاةِ",
        "answer": "and the prayer ",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wal-ṣalati",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "238"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَلًّى",
        "answer": "(as) a place of prayer",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "muṣallan",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُمٌّ",
        "answer": "Deaf",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ṣummun",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُمٌّ",
        "answer": "deaf",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṣummun",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصَابَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "strikes them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aṣābathum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصَابَهُ",
        "answer": "then fell on it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣābahu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصَابَهَا",
        "answer": "fell on it",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "aṣābahā",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصِبْهَا",
        "answer": "fall (on) it",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yuṣib'hā",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصَابَهُ",
        "answer": "and strikes him",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣābahu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصَابَهَا",
        "answer": "then falls on it",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣābahā",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَصَيِّبٍ",
        "answer": "like a rainstorm",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "kaṣayyibin",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصِيبَةٌ",
        "answer": "a misfortune",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "muṣībatun",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصُرْهُنَّ",
        "answer": "and incline them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faṣur'hunna",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصُومُوا",
        "answer": "fast",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taṣūmū",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَصُمْهُ",
        "answer": "then he should fast in it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "falyaṣum'hu",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصِّيَامُ",
        "answer": "[the] fasting",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ṣiyāmu",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصِّيَامِ",
        "answer": "(of) fasting",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-ṣiyāmi",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصِّيَامَ",
        "answer": "the fast",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-ṣiyāma",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِيَامٍ",
        "answer": "fasting",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ṣiyāmin",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصِيَامُ",
        "answer": "then a fast",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "faṣiyāmu",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "(is) the destination",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-maṣīru",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "(is) the return",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-maṣīru",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضْرِبَ",
        "answer": "set forth",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaḍriba",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اضْرِبْ",
        "answer": "Strike",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "iḍ'rib",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضُرِبَتْ",
        "answer": "And were struck",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waḍuribat",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "اضْرِبُوهُ",
        "answer": "Strike him",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "iḍ'ribūhu",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرْبًا",
        "answer": "(to) move about",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "ḍarban",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضُرُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "harms them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaḍurruhum",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُضَارَّ",
        "answer": "made to suffer",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "tuḍārra",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضَارَّ",
        "answer": "(should) be harmed",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yuḍārra",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضْطَرُّهُ",
        "answer": "I will force him",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "aḍṭarruhu",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "اضْطُرَّ",
        "answer": "(is) forced by necessity",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "uḍ'ṭurra",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالضَّرَّاءِ",
        "answer": "and [the] hardship",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wal-ḍarāi",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالضَّرَّاءُ",
        "answer": "and [the] hardship",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wal-ḍarāu",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِضَارِّينَ",
        "answer": "at all [be those who] harm",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "biḍārrīna",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضِرَارًا",
        "answer": "(to) hurt",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "ḍirāran",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُضَاعِفَهُ",
        "answer": "so (that) He multiplies it",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fayuḍāʿifahu",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضَاعِفُ",
        "answer": "gives manifold",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yuḍāʿifu",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضْعَافًا",
        "answer": "manifolds",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "aḍʿāfan",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضِعْفَيْنِ",
        "answer": "double",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ḍiʿ'fayni",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَعِيفًا",
        "answer": "weak",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ḍaʿīfan",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضُعَفَاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) weak",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ḍuʿafāu",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَّ",
        "answer": "he went astray (from)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَضِلَّ",
        "answer": "[she] errs",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taḍilla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضِلُّ",
        "answer": "He lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yuḍillu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضِلُّ",
        "answer": "He lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "yuḍillu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّلَالَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] astraying",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "l-ḍalālata",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّلَالَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] astraying",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-ḍalālata",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّالِّينَ",
        "answer": "those who went astray",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "l-ḍālīna",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَاءَتْ",
        "answer": "it illuminated",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aḍāat",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَاءَ",
        "answer": "it flashes",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "aḍāa",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُضِيعَ",
        "answer": "let go waste",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "liyuḍīʿa",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطْعَمْهُ",
        "answer": "taste it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaṭʿamhu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامٍ",
        "answer": "food",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmin",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامُ",
        "answer": "(of) feeding",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامِكَ",
        "answer": "your food",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmika",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالطَّاغُوتِ",
        "answer": "in false deities",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "bil-ṭāghūti",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّاغُوتُ",
        "answer": "(are) the evil ones",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-ṭāghūtu",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُغْيَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their transgression",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ṭugh'yānihim",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَلَّقَهَا",
        "answer": "he divorces her",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ṭallaqahā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَلَّقَهَا",
        "answer": "he divorces her",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṭallaqahā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَلَّقْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you divorce",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṭallaqtumu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَلَّقْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you divorce",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ṭallaqtumu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَلَّقْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you divorce",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṭallaqtumu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَلَّقْتُمُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "you divorce them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ṭallaqtumūhunna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّلَاقَ",
        "answer": "(on) [the] divorce ",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-ṭalāqa",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "227"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّلَاقُ",
        "answer": "The divorce",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "al-ṭalāqu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُطَلَّقَاتُ",
        "answer": "And the women who are divorced",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wal-muṭalaqātu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلْمُطَلَّقَاتِ",
        "answer": "And for the divorced women",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "walil'muṭallaqāti",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "241"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَطَلٌّ",
        "answer": "then a drizzle",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faṭallun",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَتَطْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "Do you hope",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "afataṭmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَطْمَئِنَّ",
        "answer": "to satisfy",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "liyaṭma-inna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطْهُرْنَ",
        "answer": "they are cleansed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaṭhur'na",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَهِّرَا",
        "answer": "[You both] purify",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṭahhirā",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَطَهَّرْنَ",
        "answer": "they are purified",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "taṭahharna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَطْهَرُ",
        "answer": "and more purer",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-aṭharu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُطَهَّرَةٌ",
        "answer": "purified",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "muṭahharatun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَطَهِّرِينَ",
        "answer": "those who purify themselves",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-mutaṭahirīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطُّورَ",
        "answer": "the mount",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ṭūra",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطُّورَ",
        "answer": "the mount",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-ṭūra",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَطَعْنَا",
        "answer": "and we obeyed",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-aṭaʿnā",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَطَوَّعَ",
        "answer": "voluntarily does",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "taṭawwaʿa",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَطَوَّعَ",
        "answer": "volunteers",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "taṭawwaʿa",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَطَاعُوا",
        "answer": "they are able",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "is'taṭāʿū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "they are able",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُ",
        "answer": "capable",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطَّوَّفَ",
        "answer": "he walks",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yaṭṭawwafa",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلطَّائِفِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who circumambulate",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "lilṭṭāifīna",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُطِيقُونَهُ",
        "answer": "can afford it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuṭīqūnahu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَاقَةَ",
        "answer": "strength",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṭāqata",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَاقَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) strength",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ṭāqata",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبًا",
        "answer": "(and) good",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ṭayyiban",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) good things",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ṭayyibāti",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) good",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ṭayyibāti",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) good things",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ṭayyibāti",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّيْرِ",
        "answer": "the birds",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-ṭayri",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَلَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We shaded",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waẓallalnā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلَلٍ",
        "answer": "(the) shadows",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ẓulalin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمْتُمْ",
        "answer": "[you] have wronged",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ẓalamtum",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُونَا",
        "answer": "they wronged Us",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ẓalamūnā",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "doing wrong",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaẓlimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "wronged",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "wronged",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "wronged",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "wronged",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمَ",
        "answer": "he wronged",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ẓalama",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُظْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "be wronged",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tuẓ'lamūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "wrong",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "taẓlimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُظْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be wronged",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "tuẓ'lamūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُظْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "will be wronged",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yuẓ'lamūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمَ",
        "answer": "it darkens",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "aẓlama",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more unjust",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more unjust",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلُمَاتٍ",
        "answer": "darkness[es]",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "ẓulumātin",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلُمَاتٌ",
        "answer": "darkness[es]",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "ẓulumātun",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظُّلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] darkness",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "l-ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظُّلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] darkness",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "of the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "bil-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the oppressors",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "of the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "bil-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "lilẓẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(who are) [the] wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظُنُّونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaẓunnūna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظُنُّونَ",
        "answer": "guess",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaẓunnūna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَّا",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ẓannā",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظُنُّونَ",
        "answer": "were certain",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaẓunnūna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَظَاهَرُونَ",
        "answer": "you support one another",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "taẓāharūna",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُهُورِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their backs",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ẓuhūrihim",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُهُورِهَا",
        "answer": "their backs",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ẓuhūrihā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "worship",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "you will worship",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "will you worship",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْبُدُ",
        "answer": "We will worship",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "naʿbudu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "worship Him",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَبْدِنَا",
        "answer": "Our slave",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "ʿabdinā",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "His servants",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَبْدُ",
        "answer": "and the slave",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿabdu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعَبْدِ",
        "answer": "for the slave",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿabdi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِي",
        "answer": "My servants",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "ʿibādī",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعِبَادِ",
        "answer": "to His servants",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿibādi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "207"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعَبْدٌ",
        "answer": "and a bondman",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "walaʿabdun",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَابِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) worshippers",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "ʿābidūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْثَوْا",
        "answer": "act wickedly",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taʿthaw",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعْجِبُكَ",
        "answer": "pleases you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yuʿ'jibuka",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْجَبَتْكُمْ",
        "answer": "she pleases you",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "aʿjabatkum",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْجَبَكُمْ",
        "answer": "he pleases you",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "aʿjabakum",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعَجَّلَ",
        "answer": "hurries",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "taʿajjala",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِجْلَ",
        "answer": "the calf",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-ʿij'la",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِجْلَ",
        "answer": "the calf",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-ʿij'la",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِجْلَ",
        "answer": "the calf",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-ʿij'la",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِجْلَ",
        "answer": "(love of) the calf",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-ʿij'la",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُعِدَّتْ",
        "answer": "prepared",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "uʿiddat",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعِدَّةٌ",
        "answer": "then a prescribed number",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "faʿiddatun",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعِدَّةٌ",
        "answer": "then prescribed number (should be made up)",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "faʿiddatun",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِدَّةَ",
        "answer": "the prescribed period",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-ʿidata",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْدُودَةً",
        "answer": "numbered",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "maʿdūdatan",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْدُودَاتٍ",
        "answer": "numbered",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "maʿdūdātin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْدُودَاتٍ",
        "answer": "numbered",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "maʿdūdātin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَسِهَا",
        "answer": "[and] its lentils",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waʿadasihā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدْلٌ",
        "answer": "a compensation",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ʿadlun",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدْلٌ",
        "answer": "any compensation",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ʿadlun",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعَدْلِ",
        "answer": "in justice",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿadli",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعَدْلِ",
        "answer": "with justice",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿadli",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَعَدَّ",
        "answer": "transgresses",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yataʿadda",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "transgressing",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaʿtadūna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْتَدَوْا",
        "answer": "transgressed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "iʿ'tadaw",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْتَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "transgresses",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "iʿ'tadā",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْتَدُوا",
        "answer": "transgress",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "taʿtadū",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْتَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "transgressed",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "iʿ'tadā",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْتَدُوا",
        "answer": "then you transgress",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'tadū",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْتَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "he transgressed",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "iʿ'tadā",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْتَدُوهَا",
        "answer": "transgress them",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "taʿtadūhā",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَعْتَدُوا",
        "answer": "so that you transgress",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "litaʿtadū",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "(as) enemy",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوًّا",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwan",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوًّا",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwan",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) an enemy",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعُدْوَانِ",
        "answer": "and [the] transgression",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿud'wāni",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُدْوَانَ",
        "answer": "hostility",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "ʿud'wāna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُعْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "the transgressors",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-muʿ'tadīna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادٍ",
        "answer": "transgressor",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "ʿādin",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُعَذِّبُ",
        "answer": "and He will punish",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayuʿadhibu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "torment",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(in) [the] punishment",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "and [the] punishment",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَ",
        "answer": "(from the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُرُوشِهَا",
        "answer": "its roofs",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿurūshihā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَضَهُمْ",
        "answer": "He displayed them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿaraḍahum",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَّضْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you hint",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ʿarraḍtum",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُرْضَةً",
        "answer": "an excuse",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "ʿur'ḍatan",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْرِضُونَ",
        "answer": "refusing",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "muʿ'riḍūna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَفُوا",
        "answer": "they recognized",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿarafū",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْرِفُونَهُ",
        "answer": "they recognize it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaʿrifūnahu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْرِفُونَ",
        "answer": "they recognize",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaʿrifūna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْرِفُهُمْ",
        "answer": "you recognize them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taʿrifuhum",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "with suitable",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "with due fairness",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "in a reasonable manner",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَعْرُوفٍ",
        "answer": "in a reasonable manner",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "bimaʿrūfin",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَعْرُوفٍ",
        "answer": "in a fair manner",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "bimaʿrūfin",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَعْرُوفٍ",
        "answer": "in a fair manner",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "bimaʿrūfin",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "in a fair manner",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "in a fair manner",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "in a fair manner",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "in a fair manner",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "in a fair manner",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْرُوفٍ",
        "answer": "honorably",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "maʿrūfin",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "in a fair manner ",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "241"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْرُوفًا",
        "answer": "honorable",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "maʿrūfan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْرُوفٌ",
        "answer": "kind",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "maʿrūfun",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعُرْوَةِ",
        "answer": "the handhold ",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿur'wati",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "209"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِزَّةُ",
        "answer": "(his) pride",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "l-ʿizatu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْتَزِلُوا",
        "answer": "so keep away (from)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'tazilū",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزَمُوا",
        "answer": "they resolve",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿazamū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "227"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْزِمُوا",
        "answer": "resolve (on)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taʿzimū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعُسْرَ",
        "answer": "[the] hardship",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ʿus'ra",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُسْرَةٍ",
        "answer": "in difficulty",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿus'ratin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "But perhaps",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "and perhaps",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you perhaps ",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿasaytum",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَشْرًا",
        "answer": "and ten (days)",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waʿashran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشَرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) ten (days)",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ʿasharatun",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشْرَةَ",
        "answer": "twelve",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ʿashrata",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِعْصَارٌ",
        "answer": "whirlwind",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "iʿ'ṣārun",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَصَاكَ",
        "answer": "with your staff",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "biʿaṣāka",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَصَوْا",
        "answer": "they disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿaṣaw",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَصَيْنَا",
        "answer": "and we disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waʿaṣaynā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْضُلُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "hinder them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taʿḍulūhunna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmun",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmun",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "[the] Great",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmun",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Great",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِظَامِ",
        "answer": "the bones",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiẓāmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّعَفُّفِ",
        "answer": "(their) restraint",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-taʿafufi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَفَوْنَا",
        "answer": "We forgave",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿafawnā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْفُوا",
        "answer": "So forgive",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'fū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُفِيَ",
        "answer": "is pardoned",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿufiya",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَفَا",
        "answer": "and He forgave",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "waʿafā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْفُونَ",
        "answer": "they (women) forgo (it)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yaʿfūna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْفُوَ",
        "answer": "forgoes",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaʿfuwā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْفُوا",
        "answer": "you forgo",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "taʿfū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْفُ",
        "answer": "And pardon",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-uʿ'fu",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَفْوَ",
        "answer": "The surplus",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-ʿafwa",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِقَابِ",
        "answer": "(in) retribution",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiqābi",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِقَابِ",
        "answer": "in [the] chastising",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiqābi",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَقِبَيْهِ",
        "answer": "his heels",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "ʿaqibayhi",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُقْدَةَ",
        "answer": "the knot",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿuq'data",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُقْدَةُ",
        "answer": "(is the) knot",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ʿuq'datu",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "you use reason",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "use your intellect",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَقَلُوهُ",
        "answer": "they understood it",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿaqalūhu",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "who use their intellect",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "use your intellect",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "242"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَاكِفِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who seclude themselves for devotion and prayer",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿākifīna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاكِفُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) secluded",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿākifūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "[you] know",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "[thus] they will know",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fayaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "[I] know",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "[I] know",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "and I know",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "[you] know",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمَ",
        "answer": "knew",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿalima",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you knew",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ʿalim'tumu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمُوا",
        "answer": "they knew",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ʿalimū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) know",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) know",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمْ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "taʿlam",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمْ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "taʿlam",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "that We make evident",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "linaʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "surely know",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "layaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "knowing",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمَ",
        "answer": "Knows",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ʿalima",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "and know",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "and know",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمْهُ",
        "answer": "knows it",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamhu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "and know",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "then know",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "209"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "and know",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "who know",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "and know",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "and know",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمَ",
        "answer": "Knows",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "ʿalima",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "And know",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "And know",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "knowing",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "and know",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "244"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "He knows",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "I know",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمْ",
        "answer": "And know",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lam",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "and know",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُهُ",
        "answer": "knows it",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamuhu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَلَّمَ",
        "answer": "And He taught",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "waʿallama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّمْتَنَا",
        "answer": "You have taught us",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "ʿallamtanā",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَلِّمُونَ",
        "answer": "they teach",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "yuʿallimūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَلِّمَانِ",
        "answer": "they both teach",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "yuʿallimāni",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُعَلِّمُهُمُ",
        "answer": "and will teach them",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "wayuʿallimuhumu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُعَلِّمُكُمُ",
        "answer": "and teaches you",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "wayuʿallimukumu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُعَلِّمُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and teaches you",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "wayuʿallimukum",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّمَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He (has) taught you",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "ʿallamakum",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَلَّمَهُ",
        "answer": "and taught him",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "waʿallamahu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّمَهُ",
        "answer": "(has) taught him",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "ʿallamahu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُعَلِّمُكُمُ",
        "answer": "And teaches",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "wayuʿallimukumu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَتَعَلَّمُونَ",
        "answer": "But they learn",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "fayataʿallamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَتَعَلَّمُونَ",
        "answer": "And they learn",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "wayataʿallamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "better knowing",
        "pcklId": "427",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "477",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "478",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "479",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "480",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمَ",
        "answer": "knowledge",
        "pcklId": "554",
        "tlit": "ʿil'ma",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِلْمِ",
        "answer": "the knowledge",
        "pcklId": "555",
        "tlit": "l-ʿil'mi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِلْمِ",
        "answer": "the knowledge",
        "pcklId": "556",
        "tlit": "l-ʿil'mi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِلْمِ",
        "answer": "[the] knowledge",
        "pcklId": "557",
        "tlit": "l-ʿil'mi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمِهِ",
        "answer": "His Knowledge",
        "pcklId": "558",
        "tlit": "ʿil'mihi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "659",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "660",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "661",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "662",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "663",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "664",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "665",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "227"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "666",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "244"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "667",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "668",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "669",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "670",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "760",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "(are) the All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "761",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "762",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "763",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "764",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "765",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "766",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "767",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "768",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْلُومَاتٌ",
        "answer": "well known",
        "pcklId": "822",
        "tlit": "maʿlūmātun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعْلِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they declare",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuʿ'linūna",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَلَانِيَةً",
        "answer": "and openly",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "waʿalāniyatan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the Most High",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaliyu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَمَّرُ",
        "answer": "he could be granted a life",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yuʿammaru",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَمَّرَ",
        "answer": "he should be granted life",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yuʿammara",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْتَمَرَ",
        "answer": "performs Umrah",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "iʿ'tamara",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعُمْرَةَ",
        "answer": "and the Umrah",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿum'rata",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعُمْرَةِ",
        "answer": "of the Umrah",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿum'rati",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلَ",
        "answer": "and did",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and did",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "they do",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "they do",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and did",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُنَا",
        "answer": "(are) our deeds",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "aʿmālunā",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(are) your deeds",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "aʿmālukum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their deeds",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "aʿmālahum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their deeds",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "aʿmāluhum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَهُونَ",
        "answer": "they wander blindly",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaʿmahūna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُمْيٌ",
        "answer": "blind",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿum'yun",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُمْيٌ",
        "answer": "(and) blind",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ʿum'yun",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْنَابٍ",
        "answer": "and grapevines",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿnābin",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَعْنَتَكُمْ",
        "answer": "surely He (could have) put you in difficulties",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "la-aʿnatakum",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَهُ",
        "answer": "(that) he has",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ʿindahu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَهُ",
        "answer": "with Him",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ʿindahu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "ʿindi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "ʿindi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "ʿindi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "ʿindi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِ",
        "answer": "(of)",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "ʿindi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَهِدْنَا",
        "answer": "And We made a covenant",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waʿahid'nā",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاهَدُوا",
        "answer": "they took",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ʿāhadū",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاهَدُوا",
        "answer": "they make it",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ʿāhadū",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهْدَ",
        "answer": "(the) Covenant",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ʿahda",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَهْدِي",
        "answer": "My Covenant",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "biʿahdī",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَهْدِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your covenant",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "biʿahdikum",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهْدًا",
        "answer": "a covenant",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ʿahdan",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهْدَهُ",
        "answer": "His Covenant",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ʿahdahu",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهْدًا",
        "answer": "a covenant",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ʿahdan",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهْدِي",
        "answer": "My Covenant",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ʿahdī",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَهْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their covenant",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "biʿahdihim",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادَ",
        "answer": "repeated",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿāda",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعُوذُ",
        "answer": "I seek refuge",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aʿūdhu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامٍ",
        "answer": "year(s)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿāmin",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامٍ",
        "answer": "year(s)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿāmin",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَعِينُوا",
        "answer": "And seek help",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-is'taʿīnū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَعِينُوا",
        "answer": "Seek help",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "is'taʿīnū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَوَانٌ",
        "answer": "middle aged",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿawānun",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنًا",
        "answer": "springs",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿaynan",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَغْرِبُ",
        "answer": "and the west",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wal-maghribu",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَغْرِبُ",
        "answer": "and the west",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wal-maghribu",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَغْرِبِ",
        "answer": "and the west",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wal-maghribi",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَغْرِبِ",
        "answer": "the west",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-maghribi",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "اغْتَرَفَ",
        "answer": "takes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "igh'tarafa",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُرْفَةً",
        "answer": "(in the) hollow",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ghur'fatan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَغْرَقْنَا",
        "answer": "and We drowned",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-aghraqnā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "غِشَاوَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a veil",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ghishāwatun",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَضَبٍ",
        "answer": "wrath",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "bighaḍabin",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَضَبٍ",
        "answer": "wrath",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bighaḍabin",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَضَبٍ",
        "answer": "wrath",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ghaḍabin",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "We will forgive",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "naghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَغْفِرُ",
        "answer": "Then, He will forgive",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fayaghfiru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "and forgive",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-igh'fir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَغْفِرُوا",
        "answer": "and ask forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "wa-is'taghfirū",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُفْرَانَكَ",
        "answer": "(Grant) us Your forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "ghuf'rānaka",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "192"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَغْفِرَةِ",
        "answer": "for [the] forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "bil-maghfirati",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَغْفِرَةِ",
        "answer": "and [the] forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "wal-maghfirati",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَغْفِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "and (seeking) forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "wamaghfiratun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغْفِرَةً",
        "answer": "forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "maghfiratan",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَافِلٍ",
        "answer": "unaware",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bighāfilin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَافِلٍ",
        "answer": "unaware",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "bighāfilin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَافِلٍ",
        "answer": "unaware",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "bighāfilin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَافِلٍ",
        "answer": "unaware",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bighāfilin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَافِلٍ",
        "answer": "unaware",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "bighāfilin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَلَبَتْ",
        "answer": "overcame",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ghalabat",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُلْفٌ",
        "answer": "(are) wrapped",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ghul'fun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُغْمِضُوا",
        "answer": "(with) close(d) eyes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tugh'miḍū",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَمَامَ",
        "answer": "(with) [the] clouds",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-ghamāma",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَمَامِ",
        "answer": "[the] clouds",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-ghamāmi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَنِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Sufficient",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "ghaniyyun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَنِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) Self-Sufficient",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ghaniyyun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْنِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "(that they are) self-sufficient",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "aghniyāa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيِّ",
        "answer": "the wrong",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-ghayi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "in the unseen",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bil-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْبَ",
        "answer": "(the) unseen",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ghayba",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "other (than)",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without (any)",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "to other than",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "lighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَهُ",
        "answer": "other than him",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ghayrahu",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِئَةٍ",
        "answer": "a company",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fi-atin",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِئَةً",
        "answer": "a company",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fi-atan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَحَ",
        "answer": "has",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fataḥa",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَفْتِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(that), pray for victory",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yastaftiḥūna",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a trial",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "fit'natun",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفِتْنَةُ",
        "answer": "and [the] oppression",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wal-fit'natu",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةٌ",
        "answer": "oppression",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "fit'natun",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفِتْنَةُ",
        "answer": "And [the] oppression",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wal-fit'natu",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَفَجَّرُ",
        "answer": "gush forth",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yatafajjaru",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْفَجَرَتْ",
        "answer": "Then gushed forth",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fa-infajarat",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَجْرِ",
        "answer": "[the] dawn",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-fajri",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفَحْشَاءِ",
        "answer": "and the shameful",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wal-faḥshāi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْفَحْشَاءِ",
        "answer": "to immorality",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "bil-faḥshāi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفَادُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you ransom them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tufādūhum",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَدَتْ",
        "answer": "she ransoms",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "if'tadat",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِدْيَةٌ",
        "answer": "a ransom",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fid'yatun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَفِدْيَةٌ",
        "answer": "then a ransom",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fafid'yatun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِرَاشًا",
        "answer": "a resting place",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "firāshan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَضَ",
        "answer": "undertakes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faraḍa",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْرِضُوا",
        "answer": "you specified",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tafriḍū",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَضْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have specified",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "faraḍtum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَضْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have specified",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "faraḍtum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيضَةً",
        "answer": "an obligation (dower)",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "farīḍatan",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيضَةً",
        "answer": "an obligation (dower)",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "farīḍatan",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَارِضٌ",
        "answer": "old",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "fāriḍun",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفْرِغْ",
        "answer": "Pour",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "afrigh",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We parted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faraqnā",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفَرِّقُونَ",
        "answer": "[they] causes separation",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yufarriqūna",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفَرِّقُ",
        "answer": "we make distinction",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "nufarriqu",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفَرِّقُ",
        "answer": "we make distinction",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "nufarriqu",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفُرْقَانَ",
        "answer": "and the Criterion",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wal-fur'qāna",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفُرْقَانِ",
        "answer": "and the Criterion",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wal-fur'qāni",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقٌ",
        "answer": "a party",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "farīqun",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "a party",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "farīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَفَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "So a party",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "fafarīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "and a party",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wafarīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقٌ",
        "answer": "a party",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "farīqun",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقٌ",
        "answer": "a party",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "farīqun",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "farīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "a portion",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "farīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَفَسَدَتِ",
        "answer": "certainly (would have) corrupted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lafasadati",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفْسِدُوا",
        "answer": "spread corruption",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tuf'sidū",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُفْسِدُونَ",
        "answer": "and [they] spread corruption",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wayuf'sidūna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفْسِدُ",
        "answer": "will spread corruption",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yuf'sidu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُفْسِدَ",
        "answer": "to spread corruption",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "liyuf'sida",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَسَادَ",
        "answer": "[the] corruption",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-fasāda",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْسِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the ones who spread corruption",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-muf'sidūna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "spreading corruption",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْسِدَ",
        "answer": "the corrupter",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-muf'sida",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْسُقُونَ",
        "answer": "defiantly disobeying",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yafsuqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُسُوقَ",
        "answer": "wickedness",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "fusūqa",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُسُوقٌ",
        "answer": "(is) sinful conduct",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fusūqun",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَلَ",
        "answer": "set out",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faṣala",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِصَالًا",
        "answer": "weaning",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "fiṣālan",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْفِصَامَ",
        "answer": "(will) break",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "infiṣāma",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضَّلْتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "[I] preferred you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faḍḍaltukum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضَّلْتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "[I] preferred you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "faḍḍaltukum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We (have) preferred",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "faḍḍalnā",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلُ",
        "answer": "(for the) Grace",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "faḍlu",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Grace",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "faḍlihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَضْلِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] Bounty",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-faḍli",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلًا",
        "answer": "bounty",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "faḍlan",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَضْلَ",
        "answer": "the graciousness",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-faḍla",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلٍ",
        "answer": "(of) bounty",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "faḍlin",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلٍ",
        "answer": "(of) bounty",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "faḍlin",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَضْلًا",
        "answer": "and bounty",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wafaḍlan",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلُوا",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tafʿalū",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلُوا",
        "answer": "will you do",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tafʿalū",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَافْعَلُوا",
        "answer": "so do",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fa-if'ʿalū",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) doing (it)",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yafʿalūna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلُ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yafʿalu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلُوا",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tafʿalū",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلُوا",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tafʿalū",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلْ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yafʿal",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلْنَ",
        "answer": "they do",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "faʿalna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلْنَ",
        "answer": "they do",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "faʿalna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلُ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yafʿalu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلُوا",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "tafʿalū",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلُوا",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tafʿalū",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَقْرَ",
        "answer": "[the] poverty",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-faqra",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفُقَرَاءَ",
        "answer": "(to) the poor",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-fuqarāa",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْفُقَرَاءِ",
        "answer": "For the poor",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "lil'fuqarāi",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقِعٌ",
        "answer": "bright",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fāqiʿun",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَفَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "ponder",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tatafakkarūna",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَفَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "ponder",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tatafakkarūna",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) successful",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tuf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the successful ones",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-muf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفُلْكِ",
        "answer": "and the ships",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-ful'ki",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَهَا",
        "answer": "above it",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "fawqahā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَكُمُ",
        "answer": "over you",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "fawqakumu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَكُمُ",
        "answer": "over you",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "fawqakumu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(they will be) above them",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "fawqahum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفُومِهَا",
        "answer": "[and] its garlic",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wafūmihā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاءُوا",
        "answer": "they return ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fāū",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَضْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you depart",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "afaḍtum",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفِيضُوا",
        "answer": "depart",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "afīḍū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَاضَ",
        "answer": "depart",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "afāḍa",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْبِضُ",
        "answer": "withholds",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaqbiḍu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقْبُوضَةٌ",
        "answer": "in hand",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "maqbūḍatun",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقْبَلُ",
        "answer": "will be accepted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuq'balu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقْبَلُ",
        "answer": "will be accepted",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuq'balu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقَبَّلْ",
        "answer": "Accept",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "taqabbal",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِبَلَ",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "qibala",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِ",
        "answer": "before [it]",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "qablihi",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِنَا",
        "answer": "before us",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "qablinā",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِبْلَتِهِمُ",
        "answer": "their direction of prayer",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "qib'latihimu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِبْلَةَ",
        "answer": "the direction of prayer",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "l-qib'lata",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِبْلَةً",
        "answer": "(to the) direction of prayer",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "qib'latan",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِبْلَتَكَ",
        "answer": "your direction of prayer",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "qib'lataka",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِبْلَتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their direction of prayer",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "qib'latahum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِبْلَةَ",
        "answer": "(of the) direction of prayer",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "qib'lata",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقْتِرِ",
        "answer": "the poor",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-muq'tiri",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْتُلُوا",
        "answer": "and kill",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-uq'tulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقْتُلُونَ",
        "answer": "and kill",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wayaqtulūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتَلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you killed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "qataltum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) kill",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taqtulūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلُونَ",
        "answer": "you kill(ed)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "taqtulūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلُونَ",
        "answer": "(did) you kill",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "taqtulūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقْتَلُ",
        "answer": "are slain",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yuq'talu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاقْتُلُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "And kill them",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-uq'tulūhum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْتُلُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "then kill them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fa-uq'tulūhum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَتَلَ",
        "answer": "and killed",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waqatala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَاتِلُوا",
        "answer": "And fight",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "waqātilū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَاتِلُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "fight you",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "yuqātilūnakum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقَاتِلُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "fight them",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "tuqātilūhum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَاتِلُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they fight you",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "yuqātilūkum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاتَلُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they fight you",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "qātalūkum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَاتِلُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "And fight (against) them",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "waqātilūhum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَاتِلُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(to) fight with you",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "yuqātilūnakum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَاتِلُوا",
        "answer": "And fight",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "waqātilū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "244"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُقَاتِلْ",
        "answer": "we may fight",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "nuqātil",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقَاتِلُوا",
        "answer": "you fight",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "tuqātilū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُقَاتِلَ",
        "answer": "we fight",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "nuqātila",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْتَتَلَ",
        "answer": "(would have) fought each other",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "iq'tatala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْتَتَلُوا",
        "answer": "they (would have) fought each other",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "iq'tatalū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِتَالُ",
        "answer": "[the] fighting",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "l-qitālu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِتَالٍ",
        "answer": "(concerning) fighting",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "qitālin",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِتَالٌ",
        "answer": "Fighting",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "qitālun",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِتَالُ",
        "answer": "[the] fighting",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "l-qitālu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِتَالُ",
        "answer": "the fighting",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "l-qitālu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَتْلَى",
        "answer": "(the matter of) the murdered",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-qatlā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَتْلِ",
        "answer": "[the] killing",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "l-qatli",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَتْلِ",
        "answer": "[the] killing",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "l-qatli",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِثَّائِهَا",
        "answer": "[and] its cucumbers",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waqithāihā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْدِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they have control",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaqdirūna",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَرُهُ",
        "answer": "according to his means",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "qadaruhu",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَرُهُ",
        "answer": "according to his means ",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "qadaruhu",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُقَدِّسُ",
        "answer": "and we sanctify",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wanuqaddisu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُدُسِ",
        "answer": "the Holy Spirit",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-qudusi",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُدُسِ",
        "answer": "[the] Holy",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-qudusi",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّمَتْ",
        "answer": "(of what) sent ahead",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "qaddamat",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقَدِّمُوا",
        "answer": "you send forth",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tuqaddimū",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَدِّمُوا",
        "answer": "and send forth (good deeds)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waqaddimū",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْدَامَنَا",
        "answer": "our feet",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "aqdāmanā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرُوءٍ",
        "answer": "monthly periods",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "qurūin",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنُ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-qur'ānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْرَبَا",
        "answer": "[you two] approach",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taqrabā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْرَبُوهَا",
        "answer": "approach them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taqrabūhā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْرَبُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "approach them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taqrabūhunna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَقْرَبِينَ",
        "answer": "and the near relatives",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wal-aqrabīna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَقْرَبِينَ",
        "answer": "and the relatives",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wal-aqrabīna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْرَبُ",
        "answer": "(is) nearer",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "aqrabu",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "relatives",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-qur'bā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) the near relatives",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-qur'bā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبٌ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "qarībun",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبٌ",
        "answer": "(is) near",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "qarībun",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِرَدَةً",
        "answer": "apes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qiradatan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْرَرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you ratified",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "aqrartum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقَرٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) a dwelling place",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "mus'taqarrun",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقْرِضُ",
        "answer": "will lend",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuq'riḍu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْضًا",
        "answer": "a loan",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "qarḍan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَرْيَةَ",
        "answer": "town",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-qaryata",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a township",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْسَطُ",
        "answer": "(is) more just",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aqsaṭu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَسَتْ",
        "answer": "hardened",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qasat",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَسْوَةً",
        "answer": "(in) hardness",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "qaswatan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِصَاصُ",
        "answer": "(is) the legal retribution",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-qiṣāṣu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِصَاصِ",
        "answer": "the legal retribution",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-qiṣāṣi",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِصَاصٌ",
        "answer": "(is) legal retribution",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "qiṣāṣun",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَضَىٰ",
        "answer": "He decrees",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qaḍā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَضَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you complete[d]",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "qaḍaytum",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُضِيَ",
        "answer": "and is decreed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waquḍiya",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقْطَعُونَ",
        "answer": "and [they] cut",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayaqṭaʿūna",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَقَطَّعَتْ",
        "answer": "[and] will be cut off",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wataqaṭṭaʿat",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوَاعِدَ",
        "answer": "the foundations",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-qawāʿida",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَفَّيْنَا",
        "answer": "and We followed up",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waqaffaynā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْقَلِبُ",
        "answer": "turns back",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yanqalibu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hearts",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "qulūbukum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُنَا",
        "answer": "Our hearts",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "qulūbunā",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمُ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "qulūbihimu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلْبِكَ",
        "answer": "your heart",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "qalbika",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلْبِهِ",
        "answer": "his heart",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "qalbihi",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hearts",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "qulūbukum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلْبِي",
        "answer": "my heart",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "qalbī",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلْبُهُ",
        "answer": "his heart",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "qalbuhu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقَلُّبَ",
        "answer": "(the) turning",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "taqalluba",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a few",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "so little",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "faqalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a few",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a few",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "small",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "little",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "little",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلَةٍ",
        "answer": "small",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "qalīlatin",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَانِتُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) humbly obedient",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "qānitūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَانِتِينَ",
        "answer": "devoutly obedient",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "qānitīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "238"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they (will) say",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "[thus] they will say",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "then He said",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقُلْ",
        "answer": "I say",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "aqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We said",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "waqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We said",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "waqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you said",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "qul'tum",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "And say",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "waqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "was said",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "[so] We said",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "faqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you said",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "qul'tum",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "So We said",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "faqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "says",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "says",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "says",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "So We said",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "faqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) you say",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "taqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "and speak",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "waqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولَا",
        "answer": "they [both] say",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "yaqūlā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "waqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَتِ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "waqālati",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَتِ",
        "answer": "and said",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "waqālati",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "He says",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُولُوا",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "qūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) you say",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "taqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "Will say",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "sayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "yaqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "Then said",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "(the) word",
        "pcklId": "1625",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their saying",
        "pcklId": "1626",
        "tlit": "qawlihim",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their saying",
        "pcklId": "1627",
        "tlit": "qawlihim",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلُهُ",
        "answer": "(with) his speech",
        "pcklId": "1628",
        "tlit": "qawluhu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "a saying",
        "pcklId": "1629",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلٌ",
        "answer": "A word",
        "pcklId": "1630",
        "tlit": "qawlun",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "263"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَامُوا",
        "answer": "they stand (still)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُومُوا",
        "answer": "and stand up",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waqūmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "238"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُومُونَ",
        "answer": "they can stand",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaqūmūna",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُومُ",
        "answer": "stands",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaqūmu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُقِيمُونَ",
        "answer": "and establish",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wayuqīmūna",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "And establish",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "wa-aqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "and establish",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wa-aqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "And establish",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wa-aqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقَامَ",
        "answer": "and (who) establish",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "wa-aqāma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقِيمَا",
        "answer": "they both (can) keep",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yuqīmā",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقِيمَا",
        "answer": "they both (can) keep",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yuqīmā",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقِيمَا",
        "answer": "they (will be able to) keep",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yuqīmā",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقَامُوا",
        "answer": "and established",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "wa-aqāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "277"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقْوَمُ",
        "answer": "and more upright",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "wa-aqwamu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "to his people",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "for his people",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "to his people",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for people",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "to a people",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "of [the] Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "488",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "489",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] Judgment",
        "pcklId": "490",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "491",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَيُّومُ",
        "answer": "the Sustainer of all that exists",
        "pcklId": "566",
        "tlit": "l-qayūmu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقَامِ",
        "answer": "(the) standing place",
        "pcklId": "569",
        "tlit": "maqāmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "straight",
        "pcklId": "647",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "straight",
        "pcklId": "648",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقُوَّةٍ",
        "answer": "with strength",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "biquwwatin",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقُوَّةٍ",
        "answer": "with firmness",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "biquwwatin",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُوَّةَ",
        "answer": "the power",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-quwata",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتُكَبِّرُوا",
        "answer": "and that you magnify",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "walitukabbirū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَكْبَرَ",
        "answer": "and was arrogant",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-is'takbara",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَكْبَرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you acted arrogantly",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "is'takbartum",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "(is) greater (sin)",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "(is) greater",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "(is) greater",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِبَرُ",
        "answer": "[the] old age",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "l-kibaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a great (sin)",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "kabīrun",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "kabīrun",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "large",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَبِيرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely difficult",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "lakabīratun",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَبِيرَةً",
        "answer": "certainly a great (test)",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "lakabīratan",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْتُبُونَ",
        "answer": "write",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaktubūna",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبَتْ",
        "answer": "have written",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "katabat",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُتِبَ",
        "answer": "Prescribed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kutiba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُتِبَ",
        "answer": "Prescribed",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kutiba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُتِبَ",
        "answer": "Is prescribed",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kutiba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُتِبَ",
        "answer": "was prescribed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "kutiba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبَ",
        "answer": "has ordained",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "kataba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُتِبَ",
        "answer": "Is prescribed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "kutiba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُتِبَ",
        "answer": "prescribed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "kutiba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُتِبَ",
        "answer": "was prescribed",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "kutiba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاكْتُبُوهُ",
        "answer": "then write it",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fa-uk'tubūhu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْيَكْتُبْ",
        "answer": "And let write",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "walyaktub",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْتُبَ",
        "answer": "he writes",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yaktuba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَكْتُبْ",
        "answer": "So let him write",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "falyaktub",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْتُبُوهُ",
        "answer": "you write it ",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "taktubūhu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْتُبُوهَا",
        "answer": "you write it",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "taktubūhā",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابُ",
        "answer": "(is) the book",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-kitābu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the book",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the book",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٌ",
        "answer": "a Book",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "kitābun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) Book",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book ",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "and the Book",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "wal-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابُ",
        "answer": "the prescribed term",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "l-kitābu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُتُبِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Books",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "wakutubihi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاتِبٌ",
        "answer": "a scribe",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "kātibun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاتِبٌ",
        "answer": "a scribe",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "kātibun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاتِبٌ",
        "answer": "(the) scribe",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "kātibun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاتِبًا",
        "answer": "a scribe",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "kātiban",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْتُمُونَ",
        "answer": "conceal",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taktumūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَكْتُمُوا",
        "answer": "and conceal",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wataktumū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْتُمُونَ",
        "answer": "concealing",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taktumūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَمَ",
        "answer": "concealed",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "katama",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَكْتُمُونَ",
        "answer": "surely they conceal",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "layaktumūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْتُمُونَ",
        "answer": "conceal",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaktumūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْتُمُونَ",
        "answer": "conceal",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yaktumūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْتُمْنَ",
        "answer": "they conceal",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaktum'na",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْتُمُوا",
        "answer": "conceal",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "taktumū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْتُمْهَا",
        "answer": "conceals it",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yaktum'hā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "aktharuhum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَ",
        "answer": "most",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "akthara",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرٌ",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "kathīrun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "abundant",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرَةً",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "kathīratan",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "245"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرَةً",
        "answer": "large",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "kathīratan",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْذِبُونَ",
        "answer": "[they] lie",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yakdhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "and deny",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wakadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you denied",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "kadhabtum",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرَّةً",
        "answer": "a return",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "karratan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُرْسِيُّهُ",
        "answer": "His Throne",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kur'siyyuhu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْرَهُوا",
        "answer": "you dislike",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "takrahū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُرْهٌ",
        "answer": "(is) hateful",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "kur'hun",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِكْرَاهَ",
        "answer": "compulsion",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ik'rāha",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "they earn",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَ",
        "answer": "earned",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kasaba",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَتْ",
        "answer": "it earned",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kasabat",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have earned",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kasabtum",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَتْ",
        "answer": "it earned",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kasabat",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have earned",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "kasabtum",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبُوا",
        "answer": "they earned",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "kasabū",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "202"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَتْ",
        "answer": "(have) earned",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "kasabat",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبُوا",
        "answer": "they (have) earned",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "kasabū",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have earned",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "kasabtum",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَتْ",
        "answer": "it earned",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "kasabat",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَتْ",
        "answer": "it earned",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "kasabat",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكْتَسَبَتْ",
        "answer": "it earned",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "ik'tasabat",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكْسُوهَا",
        "answer": "We cover them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "naksūhā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِسْوَتُهُنَّ",
        "answer": "and their clothing",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wakis'watuhunna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve[d]",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْفُرُونَ",
        "answer": "(can) you disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "takfurūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "who disbelieve[d]",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرُونَ",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yakfurūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَكْفُرُونَ",
        "answer": "and disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "watakfurūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved ",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "they disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرُوا",
        "answer": "they disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yakfurū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَكْفُرُونَ",
        "answer": "And they disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wayakfurūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرُ",
        "answer": "disbelieves",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yakfuru",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرَ",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "kafara",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْفُرْ",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "takfur",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرْ",
        "answer": "disbelieves",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yakfur",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرَ",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "kafara",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْفُرُونِ",
        "answer": "(be) ungrateful to Me",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "takfurūni",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve[d]",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve[d]",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve[d]",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرَ",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "kafara",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرْ",
        "answer": "disbelieves",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yakfur",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve(d)",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرَ",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "kafara",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُكَفِّرُ",
        "answer": "And He will remove",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "wayukaffiru",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرٍ",
        "answer": "disbeliever",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "kāfirin",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُفَّارًا",
        "answer": "(to) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "kuffāran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُفَّارٌ",
        "answer": "(were) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "kuffārun",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a disbeliever",
        "pcklId": "307",
        "tlit": "kāfirun",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَّارٍ",
        "answer": "ungrateful",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "kaffārin",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُفْرِهِمْ",
        "answer": "for their disbelief",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "bikuf'rihim",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُفْرِهِمْ",
        "answer": "because of their disbelief",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "bikuf'rihim",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفْرَ",
        "answer": "[the] disbelief",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "l-kuf'ra",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُفْرٌ",
        "answer": "and disbelief",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "wakuf'run",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "395",
        "tlit": "bil-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "for the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "lil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "And for the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "walil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "to the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "tlit": "lil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "And for the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "walil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "402",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْكَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "And the deniers ",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "tlit": "wal-kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(who are) disbelieving",
        "pcklId": "514",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "[the] disbelieving",
        "pcklId": "515",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "[the] disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "516",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافَّةً",
        "answer": "completely",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "kāffatan",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "208"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَيَكْفِيكَهُمُ",
        "answer": "So will suffice you against them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fasayakfīkahumu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُكَلَّفُ",
        "answer": "is burdened",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tukallafu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَلِّفُ",
        "answer": "burden",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yukallifu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "of every",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّهَا",
        "answer": "all of them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kullahā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "All",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "with all",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِكُلٍّ",
        "answer": "And for everyone",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "walikullin",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "of every",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "each",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "each",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "all (kinds)",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "of every",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "All",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّمَا",
        "answer": "Whenever",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "kullamā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّمَا",
        "answer": "Every time",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "kullamā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَكُلَّمَا",
        "answer": "Is it (not) so (that) whenever",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "afakullamā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَكُلَّمَا",
        "answer": "And is (it not that) whenever",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "awakullamā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَلِّمُنَا",
        "answer": "speaks to us",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yukallimunā",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَلِّمُهُمُ",
        "answer": "will speak to them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yukallimuhumu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلَّمَ",
        "answer": "spoke",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kallama",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "253"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلَامَ",
        "answer": "(the) words",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "kalāma",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَاتٍ",
        "answer": "words",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "kalimātin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكَلِمَاتٍ",
        "answer": "with words",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "bikalimātin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتُكْمِلُوا",
        "answer": "so that you complete",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "walituk'milū",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَامِلَيْنِ",
        "answer": "complete",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kāmilayni",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَامِلَةٌ",
        "answer": "in all",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kāmilatun",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْنَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you conceal it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aknantum",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكَادُ",
        "answer": "Almost",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yakādu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَادُوا",
        "answer": "they were near",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kādū",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were they",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "While you were",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wakuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you [were]",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and became",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَكُونَا",
        "answer": "lest you [both] be",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fatakūnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَا",
        "answer": "they [both] were",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "kānā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "takūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "used to",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "surely you would have been",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "lakuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُونُوا",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "kūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكُونَ",
        "answer": "I be",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "akūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(there) has been",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "though they used to",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "it is",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْ",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "kun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَكُونُ",
        "answer": "and it becomes",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "fayakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "were you",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُونُوا",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "kūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he was",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were used to",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "so that you will be",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "litakūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَكُونَ",
        "answer": "and will be",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "wayakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you were used to",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "it was",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "will",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "takūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "you will be",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "takūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you (all) are",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونَ",
        "answer": "will be",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "takūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "[were]",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "used to",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَ",
        "answer": "(there) is",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "takūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَكُونَ",
        "answer": "and becomes",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "wayakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُنْ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "yakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "Was",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّ",
        "answer": "they",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "kunna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "[is]",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "takūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "239"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُ",
        "answer": "can be",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "yakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَ",
        "answer": "it be",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "takūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "278"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونَا",
        "answer": "there are",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "yakūnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "takūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "How",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْبَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) understanding",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-albābi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْبَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) understanding",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-albābi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْبَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) understanding",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-albābi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "269"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِثْتَ",
        "answer": "(have) you remained",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "labith'ta",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِثْتُ",
        "answer": "I remained",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "labith'tu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِثْتَ",
        "answer": "you (have) remained",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "labith'ta",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَلْبِسُوا",
        "answer": "mix",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "talbisū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَاسٌ",
        "answer": "(are) garments",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "libāsun",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَاسٌ",
        "answer": "(are) garments",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "libāsun",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلْحَافًا",
        "answer": "with importunity",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "il'ḥāfan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَحْمَ",
        "answer": "and flesh",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "walaḥma",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَحْمًا",
        "answer": "(with) flesh",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "laḥman",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَدُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the most quarrelsome",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aladdu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعَنَهُمُ",
        "answer": "has cursed them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "laʿanahumu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْعَنُهُمُ",
        "answer": "curses them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yalʿanuhumu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَلْعَنُهُمُ",
        "answer": "and curse them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wayalʿanuhumu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَعْنَةُ",
        "answer": "So (the) curse",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "falaʿnatu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعْنَةُ",
        "answer": "(is the) curse",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "laʿnatu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّاعِنُونَ",
        "answer": "the ones who curse",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-lāʿinūna",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّغْوِ",
        "answer": "for (what is) unintentional",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bil-laghwi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْفَيْنَا",
        "answer": "we found",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "alfaynā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقُوا",
        "answer": "they meet",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "laqū",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقُوا",
        "answer": "they meet",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "laqū",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُلْقُوا",
        "answer": "throw (yourselves)",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "tul'qū",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَلَقَّىٰ",
        "answer": "Then received",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "fatalaqqā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلَاقُو",
        "answer": "will meet",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "mulāqū",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلَاقُوهُ",
        "answer": "(will) meet Him",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "mulāqūhu",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلَاقُو",
        "answer": "(would) meet",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "mulāqū",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَوْنُهَا",
        "answer": "(is) its color",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lawnuhā",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَوْنُهَا",
        "answer": "(in) its color",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "lawnuhā",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَتِ",
        "answer": "Not",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "laysati",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَتِ",
        "answer": "Not",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "laysati",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "It is not",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "And it is not",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "walaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Not is",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "then he is not",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "falaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَسْتُمْ",
        "answer": "while you (would) not",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "walastum",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Not",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "then not",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "falaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "of the night",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "by night",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bi-al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْلَةً",
        "answer": "nights",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "laylatan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْلَةَ",
        "answer": "(in the) nights",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "laylata",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِائَةَ",
        "answer": "(for) a hundred",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "mi-ata",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِائَةَ",
        "answer": "one hundred",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "mi-ata",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِائَةُ",
        "answer": "hundred",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "mi-atu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأُمَتِّعُهُ",
        "answer": "[then] I will grant him enjoyment",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-umattiʿuhu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَتِّعُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "And make provision for them ",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wamattiʿūhunna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمَتَّعَ",
        "answer": "took advantage",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tamattaʿa",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَتَاعٌ",
        "answer": "and a provision",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wamatāʿun",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَاعًا",
        "answer": "a provision",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "matāʿan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَاعًا",
        "answer": "provision",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "matāʿan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَاعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a provision",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "matāʿun",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "241"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلِهِ",
        "answer": "like it",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "mith'lihi",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلِهَا",
        "answer": "similar (to) it",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mith'lihā",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَ",
        "answer": "similar",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "mith'la",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَ",
        "answer": "similar",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mith'la",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمِثْلِ",
        "answer": "in (the) like",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "bimith'li",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمِثْلِ",
        "answer": "in (the) same manner",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "bimith'li",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُ",
        "answer": "(is the) like",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "mith'lu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُ",
        "answer": "(is a duty) like",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "mith'lu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُ",
        "answer": "(is) like",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "mith'lu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "Their example",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "mathaluhum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "(is) like (the) example",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلًا",
        "answer": "an example",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "mathalan",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلًا",
        "answer": "example",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "mathalan",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَثَلُ",
        "answer": "And (the) example",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "wamathalu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "(is) like (the) example",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلُ",
        "answer": "like (came to)",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "mathalu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلُ",
        "answer": "Example",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "mathalu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "(is) like",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَثَلُهُ",
        "answer": "Then his example",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "famathaluhu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "(is) like",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَثَلُ",
        "answer": "And (the) example",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "wamathalu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "(is) like",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْحَقُ",
        "answer": "Destroys",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yamḥaqu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "276"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَمُدُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "and prolongs them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayamudduhum",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَامْرَأَتَانِ",
        "answer": "and two women",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-im'ra-atāni",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَرْءِ",
        "answer": "the man",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-mari",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّ",
        "answer": "passed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "marra",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّتَانِ",
        "answer": "(is) twice",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "marratāni",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَضٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a disease",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "maraḍun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَضًا",
        "answer": "(in) disease",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "maraḍan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرِيضًا",
        "answer": "sick",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "marīḍan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرِيضًا",
        "answer": "sick",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "marīḍan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرِيضًا",
        "answer": "ill",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "marīḍan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُمْتَرِينَ",
        "answer": "the doubters",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-mum'tarīna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمَسَّنَا",
        "answer": "will touch us",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tamassanā",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "Touched them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "massathumu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمَسُّوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "you have touched",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tamassūhunna",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمَسُّوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "you (have) touched them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tamassūhunna",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسِّ",
        "answer": "(his) touch",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-masi",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمْسِكُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "then retain them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-amsikūhunna",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُمْسِكُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "retain them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tum'sikūhunna",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَمْسَكَ",
        "answer": "he grasped",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "is'tamsaka",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِمْسَاكٌ",
        "answer": "Then to retain",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "fa-im'sākun",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "229"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَشَوْا",
        "answer": "they walk",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "mashaw",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِصْرًا",
        "answer": "(to) a city",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "miṣ'ran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَإِ",
        "answer": "the chiefs",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-mala-i",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكِ",
        "answer": "(the) kingdom",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "mul'ki",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Kingdom",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْكُ",
        "answer": "the kingship",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "l-mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمُلْكِ",
        "answer": "to kingship",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "bil-mul'ki",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكَهُ",
        "answer": "His kingdom",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "mul'kahu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his kingship",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "mul'kihi",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْكَ",
        "answer": "the kingdom",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-mul'ka",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْكَ",
        "answer": "the kingdom",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-mul'ka",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلِكًا",
        "answer": "a king",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "malikan",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلِكًا",
        "answer": "(as) a king",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "malikan",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "to the angels",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "lil'malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "the angels",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "l-malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "to the angels",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "lil'malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَلَائِكَتِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Angels",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "wamalāikatihi",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَكَيْنِ",
        "answer": "the two angels",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "l-malakayni",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "and the Angels",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "wal-malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "and the Angels",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "wal-malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَلَائِكَةُ",
        "answer": "and the Angels",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "wal-malāikatu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةُ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "l-malāikatu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَلَائِكَتِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Angels",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "wamalāikatihi",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْيُمْلِلِ",
        "answer": "and let dictate",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "walyum'lili",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُمِلَّ",
        "answer": "(can) dictate",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yumilla",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيُمْلِلْ",
        "answer": "then let dictate",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "falyum'lil",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِلَّتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their religion",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "millatahum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِلَّةِ",
        "answer": "(the) religion",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "millati",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِلَّةَ",
        "answer": "(the) religion",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "millata",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَعَ",
        "answer": "prevents",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "manaʿa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَنَّ",
        "answer": "[the] manna",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-mana",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنًّا",
        "answer": "(with) reminders of generosity",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "mannan",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَنِّ",
        "answer": "with reminders (of it)",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "bil-mani",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَمَنَّوُا",
        "answer": "then wish",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fatamannawū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَمَنَّوْهُ",
        "answer": "they wish for it",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yatamannawhu",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَانِيَّ",
        "answer": "wishful thinking",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "amāniyya",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَانِيُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their wishful thinking",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "amāniyyuhum",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمِهَادُ",
        "answer": "[the] resting-place",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-mihādu",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمُوتُنَّ",
        "answer": "(should) you die",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tamūtunna",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَاتُوا",
        "answer": "and die[d]",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wamātū",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَمُتْ",
        "answer": "then dies",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fayamut",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُوتُوا",
        "answer": "Die",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "mūtū",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُمِيتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will cause you to die",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yumītukum",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُمِيتُ",
        "answer": "and causes death",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "wayumītu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُمِيتُ",
        "answer": "and cause death",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "wa-umītu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَاتَهُ",
        "answer": "Then he was made to die",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "fa-amātahu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتِ",
        "answer": "[the] death",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "l-mawti",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your death",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "mawtikum",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَ",
        "answer": "(for) [the] death",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "l-mawta",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتُ",
        "answer": "[the] death",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-mawtu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْتِهَا",
        "answer": "its death",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "mawtihā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتُ",
        "answer": "[the] death",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-mawtu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] death",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "l-mawti",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْتِهَا",
        "answer": "its death",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "mawtihā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَاتًا",
        "answer": "dead",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "amwātan",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "the dead",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "l-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَاتٌ",
        "answer": "(They are) dead",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "amwātun",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "(to) the dead",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "l-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَيْتَةَ",
        "answer": "the dead animals",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "l-maytata",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْوَالِ",
        "answer": "[the] wealth",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-amwāli",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَالَ",
        "answer": "the wealth",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-māla",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your properties",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "amwālakum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالِ",
        "answer": "(the) wealth",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "amwāli",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَالِ",
        "answer": "[the] wealth",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-māli",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their wealth",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "amwālahum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their wealth",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "amwālahum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَالَهُ",
        "answer": "his wealth",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mālahu",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالَهُمُ",
        "answer": "their wealth",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "amwālahumu",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their wealth",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "amwālahum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your capital ",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "amwālikum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "279"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءً",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "māan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءُ",
        "answer": "[the] water",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-māu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءٍ",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "māin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْبِئُونِي",
        "answer": "Inform Me",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "anbiūnī",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْبِئْهُمْ",
        "answer": "Inform them",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "anbi'hum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْبَأَهُمْ",
        "answer": "he had informed them",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "anba-ahum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيِّينَ",
        "answer": "the Prophets",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-nabiyīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْبِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "(the) Prophets",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "anbiyāa",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيُّونَ",
        "answer": "(to) the Prophets",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "l-nabiyūna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّبِيِّينَ",
        "answer": "and the Prophets",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "wal-nabiyīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيِّينَ",
        "answer": "[the] Prophets",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-nabiyīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَبِيٍّ",
        "answer": "to a Prophet",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "linabiyyin",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبِيُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Prophet",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "nabiyyuhum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبِيُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Prophet",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "nabiyyuhum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْبِتُ",
        "answer": "grows",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tunbitu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْبَتَتْ",
        "answer": "which grows",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "anbatat",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَذَهُ",
        "answer": "threw it away",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nabadhahu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَذَ",
        "answer": "threw away",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "nabadha",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجَّيْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We saved you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "najjaynākum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْجَيْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "then We saved you",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "fa-anjaynākum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخِيلٍ",
        "answer": "date-palms",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "nakhīlin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْدَادًا",
        "answer": "rivals",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "andādan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْدَادًا",
        "answer": "equals",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "andādan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنِدَاءً",
        "answer": "and cries ",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wanidāan",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذَرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you vow",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nadhartum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَأَنْذَرْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "whether you warn them",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "a-andhartahum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْذِرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "you warn them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tundhir'hum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذْرٍ",
        "answer": "vow(s)",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "nadhrin",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَذِيرًا",
        "answer": "and (as) a warner",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "wanadhīran",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُنْذِرِينَ",
        "answer": "and (as) warners",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "wamundhirīna",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have revealed",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "nazzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزِّلَ",
        "answer": "sends down",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yunazzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلَهُ",
        "answer": "brought it down",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "nazzalahu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزَّلَ",
        "answer": "(there should) be sent down",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yunazzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلَ",
        "answer": "revealed",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "nazzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "(is) sent down",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was sent down",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "and sent down",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "wa-anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْتُ",
        "answer": "I have sent down",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "anzaltu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We sent down",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "wa-anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "so We sent down",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "fa-anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We revealed",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was sent down",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "(is) revealed",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We revealed",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "(has) sent down",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "(has) revealed",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "and sent down",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "wa-anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "(is) revealed",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "285"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَنْسَخْ",
        "answer": "We abrogate",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nansakh",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَاسِكَنَا",
        "answer": "our ways of worship",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "manāsikanā",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَاسِكَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your acts of worship",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "manāsikakum",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُسُكٍ",
        "answer": "sacrifice",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nusukin",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّسْلَ",
        "answer": "and progeny",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-nasla",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِسَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your women",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nisāakum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِسَائِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your wives",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "nisāikum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّسَاءَ",
        "answer": "[the] women",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-nisāa",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "222"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِسَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "Your wives",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nisāukum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِسَائِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their wives",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nisāihim",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "226"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّسَاءَ",
        "answer": "the women",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-nisāa",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّسَاءَ",
        "answer": "[the] women",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-nisāa",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّسَاءِ",
        "answer": "[to] the women",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-nisāi",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّسَاءَ",
        "answer": "[the] women",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-nisāa",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَنْسَوْنَ",
        "answer": "and you forget",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "watansawna",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْسَوُا",
        "answer": "forget",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tansawū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسِينَا",
        "answer": "we forget",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nasīnā",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُنْسِهَا",
        "answer": "[We] cause it to be forgotten",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "nunsihā",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُنْشِزُهَا",
        "answer": "We raise them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nunshizuhā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيبٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a share",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "naṣībun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "202"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "will be helped",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yunṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "will be helped",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yunṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "will be helped",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yunṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَانْصُرْنَا",
        "answer": "and help us",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-unṣur'nā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْصُرْنَا",
        "answer": "so help us",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fa-unṣur'nā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرُ",
        "answer": "[will] (the) help",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "naṣru",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرَ",
        "answer": "help",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "naṣra",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "214"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the Christians",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "wal-naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "(a) Christian[s]",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "the Christians",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "the Christians",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "the Christians",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "Christians",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "Christians",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرٍ",
        "answer": "any helper",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "naṣīrin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرٍ",
        "answer": "any helper",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "naṣīrin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْصَارٍ",
        "answer": "helpers",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "anṣārin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنِصْفُ",
        "answer": "then (give) half",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faniṣ'fu",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) looking",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) looking",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْنَا",
        "answer": "Unzurna",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "unẓur'nā",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they waiting",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْظُرْ",
        "answer": "Then look",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fa-unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَانْظُرْ",
        "answer": "and look",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَانْظُرْ",
        "answer": "And look",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْظَرُونَ",
        "answer": "will be reprieved",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "yunẓarūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَظِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "then postponement",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "fanaẓiratun",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاظِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) those who see (it). ",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "l-nāẓirīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْعِقُ",
        "answer": "shouts",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yanʿiqu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنِعِمَّا",
        "answer": "then good",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faniʿimmā",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "271"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَمْتُ",
        "answer": "I bestowed",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "anʿamtu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَمْتُ",
        "answer": "I bestowed",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "anʿamtu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَمْتُ",
        "answer": "I bestowed",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "anʿamtu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتِيَ",
        "answer": "My Favor",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matiya",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتِيَ",
        "answer": "My Favor",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matiya",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتِيَ",
        "answer": "My Favor",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matiya",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتِي",
        "answer": "My favor",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matī",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَةَ",
        "answer": "Favor",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "niʿ'mata",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "211"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتَ",
        "answer": "(the) Favors",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "niʿ'mata",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "anfusakum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٌ",
        "answer": "any soul",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nafsun",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "(another) soul",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "anfusakum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "anfusakum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(to) themselves",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسًا",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "nafsan",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "anfusakum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "anfusakum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسُكُمُ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "anfusukumu",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "for yourselves",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "li-anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٌ",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "nafsun",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "(another) soul",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسَهُ",
        "answer": "himself",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "nafsahu",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَنْفُسِ",
        "answer": "and [the] lives",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wal-anfusi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "anfusakum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسَهُ",
        "answer": "his own self",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "nafsahu",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "207"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "for yourselves",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "li-anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَنْفُسِهِنَّ",
        "answer": "concerning themselves",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "bi-anfusihinna",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسَهُ",
        "answer": "himself",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "nafsahu",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٌ",
        "answer": "any soul",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "nafsun",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَنْفُسِهِنَّ",
        "answer": "for themselves",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "bi-anfusihinna",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِنَّ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "anfusihinna",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِنَّ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "anfusihinna",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their (inner) souls",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلِأَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "then it is for yourself",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "fali-anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "soul",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "284"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسًا",
        "answer": "any soul",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "nafsan",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْفَعُهُمْ",
        "answer": "profits them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yanfaʿuhum",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْفَعُهَا",
        "answer": "will benefit it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tanfaʿuhā",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْفَعُ",
        "answer": "benefits",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yanfaʿu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَنَافِعُ",
        "answer": "and (some) benefits",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wamanāfiʿu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْعِهِمَا",
        "answer": "(the) benefit of (the) two",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "nafʿihimā",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "they spend",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "And spend",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-anfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "they (should) spend",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفَقْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you spend",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "anfaqtum",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "they (should) spend",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "Spend",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "anfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "spend",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "spend",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفَقُوا",
        "answer": "they spend",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "anfaqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "262"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُ",
        "answer": "spends",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yunfiqu",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "spend",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "Spend",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "anfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "you spend",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "tunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفَقْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you spend",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "anfaqtum",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "you spend",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tunfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "you spend",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "you spend",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tunfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "you spend",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "tunfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "spend",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفَقَةٍ",
        "answer": "(your) expenditures",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "nafaqatin",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَقْصٍ",
        "answer": "and loss",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wanaqṣin",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْقُضُونَ",
        "answer": "break",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yanquḍūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْكِحُوا",
        "answer": "[you] marry",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tankiḥū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْكِحَ",
        "answer": "she marries",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tankiḥa",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْكِحْنَ",
        "answer": "(from) marrying",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yankiḥ'na",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْكِحُوا",
        "answer": "give in marriage (your women)",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "tunkiḥū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّكَاحِ",
        "answer": "(of) marriage",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-nikāḥi",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّكَاحِ",
        "answer": "(of) the marriage",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-nikāḥi",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكَالًا",
        "answer": "a deterrent punishment",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "nakālan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "and the day",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "and day",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "274"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "[the] rivers",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِنَهَرٍ",
        "answer": "with a river",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "binaharin",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْتَهَوْا",
        "answer": "they cease",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "intahaw",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "192"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْتَهَوْا",
        "answer": "they cease",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "intahaw",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْتَهَىٰ",
        "answer": "and he refrained",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "fa-intahā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارًا",
        "answer": "a fire",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nāran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارَ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-nāra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارُ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-nāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارَ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-nāra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "217"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارٌ",
        "answer": "(is) fire",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "nārun",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِنُورِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their light",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "binūrihim",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّورِ",
        "answer": "[the] light",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "l-nūri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّورِ",
        "answer": "the light",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-nūri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "(is) [the] men",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "[the] people",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "to [the] people",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the mankind",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] mankind",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for the mankind",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for mankind",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the mankind",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(is) to [the] mankind",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "bil-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for the people",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "to the people",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "and the mankind",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wal-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "[the] people",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the mankind",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for mankind",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for [the] people",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for the people",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "207"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "[the] people",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for [the] people",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for the people",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "221"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "[the] people",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "[the] mankind",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "[the] people ",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for the people",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(by) the people",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "273"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "sleep",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nawmun",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنَالُ",
        "answer": "reach",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yanālu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَاتُوا",
        "answer": "Bring",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "hātū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْبِطُوا",
        "answer": "Go down (all of you)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ih'biṭū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْبِطُوا",
        "answer": "Go down",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ih'biṭū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْبِطُوا",
        "answer": "Go down",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ih'biṭū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْبِطُ",
        "answer": "fall down",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yahbiṭu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَاجَرُوا",
        "answer": "emigrated",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "hājarū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "218"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَهْدِي",
        "answer": "and He guides",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wayahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "He guides",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَى",
        "answer": "guided",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "hadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "He guided you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "hadākum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "He (has) guided you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "hadākum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَهَدَى",
        "answer": "And guided",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fahadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guides",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guides",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(would be) guided",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "tahtadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَهْتَدُوا",
        "answer": "(then) you will be guided",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "tahtadū",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْتَدَوْا",
        "answer": "they are (rightly) guided",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "ih'tadaw",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) guided",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "tahtadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "were they guided",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "yahtadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهَدْيِ",
        "answer": "the sacrificial animal",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "l-hadyi",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهَدْيُ",
        "answer": "the sacrificial animal",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "l-hadyu",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهَدْيِ",
        "answer": "the sacrificial animal",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "l-hadyi",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "a Guidance",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "Guidance",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "for [the] guidance",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "bil-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "Guidance",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدَايَ",
        "answer": "My Guidance",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "hudāya",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهُدًى",
        "answer": "and a guidance",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "wahudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدَى",
        "answer": "(the) Guidance",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) the Guidance",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the Guidance",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "wal-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "for [the] Guidance",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "bil-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "a Guidance",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "[the] Guidance",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their guidance",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "hudāhum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "guided-ones",
        "pcklId": "298",
        "tlit": "muh'tadīna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) surely be those who are guided",
        "pcklId": "299",
        "tlit": "lamuh'tadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the guided ones",
        "pcklId": "300",
        "tlit": "l-muh'tadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَهْزِئُ",
        "answer": "mocks",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yastahzi-u",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُزُوًا",
        "answer": "(in) ridicule",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "huzuwan",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُزُوًا",
        "answer": "(in) jest",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "huzuwan",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَهْزِئُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) mockers",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "mus'tahziūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَهَزَمُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "So they defeated them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fahazamūhum",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "251"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُهْلِكَ",
        "answer": "and destroys",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wayuh'lika",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّهْلُكَةِ",
        "answer": "[the] destruction",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-tahlukati",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُهِلَّ",
        "answer": "has been dedicated",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "uhilla",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَهِلَّةِ",
        "answer": "the new moons",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-ahilati",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَادُوا",
        "answer": "became Jews",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "hādū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُودًا",
        "answer": "(a) Jew[s]",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "hūdan",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُودًا",
        "answer": "Jews",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "hūdan",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُودًا",
        "answer": "Jews",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "hūdan",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهِينٌ",
        "answer": "humiliating",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "muhīnun",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَهْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "desire",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tahwā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْوَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their desires",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ahwāahum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْوَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their desires",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ahwāahum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابِلٌ",
        "answer": "heavy rain",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wābilun",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابِلٌ",
        "answer": "heavy rain",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wābilun",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابِلٌ",
        "answer": "heavy rain",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wābilun",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "265"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقِهِ",
        "answer": "its ratification",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mīthāqihi",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your covenant",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "mīthāqakum",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقَ",
        "answer": "(the) covenant",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mīthāqa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your covenant",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "mīthāqakum",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your covenant",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "mīthāqakum",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوُثْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "[the] firm",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-wuth'qā",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "256"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَتَجِدَنَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "And surely you will find them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "walatajidannahum",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُوهُ",
        "answer": "you will find it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tajidūhu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدْ",
        "answer": "find ",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yajid",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُوا",
        "answer": "you find",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tajidū",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهَهُ",
        "answer": "his face",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wajhahu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهُ",
        "answer": "(is the) face",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wajhu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهِكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your face",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wajhika",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهَكَ",
        "answer": "your face",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wajhaka",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your faces",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wujūhakum",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهَكَ",
        "answer": "your face",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wajhaka",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهَكَ",
        "answer": "your face",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wajhaka",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your faces",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wujūhakum",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your faces",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wujūhakum",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهِ",
        "answer": "(the) face",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wajhi",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "وِجْهَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a direction ",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "wij'hatun",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدٍ",
        "answer": "(of) one (kind)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wāḥidin",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدًا",
        "answer": "One",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wāḥidan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدٌ",
        "answer": "one (only)",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wāḥidun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "213"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوَدُّ",
        "answer": "Loves",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yawaddu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوَدُّ",
        "answer": "like",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yawaddu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَدَّ",
        "answer": "Wish[ed]",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wadda",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَوَدُّ",
        "answer": "Would like",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ayawaddu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "266"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَذَرُونَ",
        "answer": "and leave behind",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayadharūna",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَذَرُونَ",
        "answer": "and leave behind",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wayadharūna",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذَرُوا",
        "answer": "and give up",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wadharū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "278"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَارِثِ",
        "answer": "the (father s) heir",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-wārithi",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَاءَهُ",
        "answer": "(is) besides it",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "warāahu",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَاءَ",
        "answer": "behind",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "warāa",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَطًا",
        "answer": "(of the) middle way",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wasaṭan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوُسْطَىٰ",
        "answer": "[the] middle",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-wus'ṭā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "238"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسِعَ",
        "answer": "Extends",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wasiʿa",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعَةً",
        "answer": "abundance",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "saʿatan",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُسْعَهَا",
        "answer": "its capacity",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wus'ʿahā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُسْعَهَا",
        "answer": "its capacity",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wus'ʿahā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسِعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Encompassing",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wāsiʿun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسِعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Encompassing",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wāsiʿun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسِعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Encompassing",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wāsiʿun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "261"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسِعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Encompassing",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wāsiʿun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُوسِعِ",
        "answer": "the wealthy",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-mūsiʿi",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "236"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِنَةٌ",
        "answer": "slumber",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sinatun",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِيَةَ",
        "answer": "blemish",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shiyata",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوصَلَ",
        "answer": "be joined",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yūṣala",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوَصَّىٰ",
        "answer": "And enjoined",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wawaṣṣā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَصِيَّةُ",
        "answer": "(making) the will",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-waṣiyatu",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصِيَّةً",
        "answer": "(should make) a will",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "waṣiyyatan",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُوصٍ",
        "answer": "(the) testator",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "mūṣin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعِدُكُمُ",
        "answer": "promises you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaʿidukumu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعِدُكُمْ",
        "answer": "promises you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaʿidukum",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "268"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعَدْنَا",
        "answer": "We appointed",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "wāʿadnā",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوَاعِدُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "promise them (widows)",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "tuwāʿidūhunna",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "235"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعِظُكُمْ",
        "answer": "He instructs you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaʿiẓukum",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوعَظُ",
        "answer": "is admonished",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yūʿaẓu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَوْعِظَةً",
        "answer": "and an admonition",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wamawʿiẓatan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْعِظَةٌ",
        "answer": "(the) admonition",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "mawʿiẓatun",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "275"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوَفَّ",
        "answer": "will be repaid in full",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuwaffa",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "272"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوَفَّىٰ",
        "answer": "(will be) repaid in full",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tuwaffā",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْفُوا",
        "answer": "and fulfill",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wa-awfū",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوفِ",
        "answer": "I will fulfill",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ūfi",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتَوَفَّوْنَ",
        "answer": "pass away",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yutawaffawna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "234"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتَوَفَّوْنَ",
        "answer": "die",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yutawaffawna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُوفُونَ",
        "answer": "and those who fulfill",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wal-mūfūna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوَاقِيتُ",
        "answer": "(are) indicators of periods",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "mawāqītu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَوْقَدَ",
        "answer": "kindled",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "is'tawqada",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُودُهَا",
        "answer": "[its] fuel",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waqūduhā",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِنَا",
        "answer": "and save us",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waqinā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "become righteous",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "then fear",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "fa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَّقُونِ",
        "answer": "fear [Me]",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fa-ittaqūni",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(would become) righteous",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "tattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "and feared (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(become) righteous",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "tattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(become) righteous",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "tattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(become) righteous",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَىٰ",
        "answer": "fears (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ittaqā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُونِ",
        "answer": "And fear Me",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqūni",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَىٰ",
        "answer": "fears",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ittaqā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقِ",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ittaqi",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And be conscious",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "223"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "and be righteous",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "watattaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "278"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْيَتَّقِ",
        "answer": "and let him fear",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "walyattaqi",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "and fear",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْيَتَّقِ",
        "answer": "And let him fear",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "walyattaqi",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "283"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّقْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) righteousness",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "l-taqwā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلتَّقْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "to [the] righteousness",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "lilttaqwā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "for the God-conscious",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "lil'muttaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "lil'muttaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the righteous",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous ones",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "those who fear (Him)",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "241"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِالْوَالِدَيْنِ",
        "answer": "and with [the] parents",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wabil-wālidayni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْوَالِدَيْنِ",
        "answer": "for the parents",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "lil'wālidayni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلِلْوَالِدَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(is) for parents",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "falil'wālidayni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَدًا",
        "answer": "a son",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "waladan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلَادَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "their children",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "awlādahunna",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِوَلَدِهَا",
        "answer": "because of her child",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "biwaladihā",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِوَلَدِهِ",
        "answer": "because of his child",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "biwaladihi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلَادَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your child",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "awlādakum",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْوَالِدَاتُ",
        "answer": "And the mothers",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "wal-wālidātu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالِدَةٌ",
        "answer": "(the) mother",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "wālidatun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْلُودِ",
        "answer": "the father",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "l-mawlūdi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْلُودٌ",
        "answer": "(the) father",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "mawlūdun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "233"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوَلُّوا",
        "answer": "you turn",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tuwallū",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَّاهُمْ",
        "answer": "(has) turned them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wallāhum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَنُوَلِّيَنَّكَ",
        "answer": "So We will surely turn you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "falanuwalliyannaka",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَلِّ",
        "answer": "So turn",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fawalli",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَلُّوا",
        "answer": "[so] turn",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fawallū",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَلِّ",
        "answer": "[so] turn",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fawalli",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَلِّ",
        "answer": "[so] turn",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fawalli",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَلُّوا",
        "answer": "[so] turn",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fawallū",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوَلُّوا",
        "answer": "you turn",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tuwallū",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you turned away",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "tawallaytum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you turned away",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "tawallaytum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "tawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "he turns away",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "tawallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "they turned away",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "tawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "246"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْلَانَا",
        "answer": "our Protector",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "mawlānā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "286"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٍّ",
        "answer": "protector",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "waliyyin",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٍّ",
        "answer": "protector",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "waliyyin",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيُّ",
        "answer": "(is the) Protecting Guardian",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "waliyyu",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاؤُهُمُ",
        "answer": "their guardians",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "awliyāuhumu",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيُّهُ",
        "answer": "his guardian",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "waliyyuhu",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "282"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُوَلِّيهَا",
        "answer": "turns towards it",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "muwallīhā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَتَامَىٰ",
        "answer": "and [the] orphans",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-yatāmā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَتَامَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the orphans",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-yatāmā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَتَامَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the orphans",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-yatāmā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "215"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَتَامَىٰ",
        "answer": "the orphans",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-yatāmā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "220"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْهَا",
        "answer": "(of) them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yadayhā",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their (own) hands",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bi-aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْهِ",
        "answer": "before it",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yadayhi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَيْدِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "[with your hands]",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bi-aydīkum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَدِهِ",
        "answer": "in whose hands",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "biyadihi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "237"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَدِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his hand",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "biyadihi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "255"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَيْسَرَ",
        "answer": "(can be) obtained with ease",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "is'taysara",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَيْسَرَ",
        "answer": "(can be) obtained with ease",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "is'taysara",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَيْسِرِ",
        "answer": "and [the] games of chance",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wal-maysiri",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "219"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَيْسَرَةٍ",
        "answer": "ease",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "maysaratin",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيُسْرَ",
        "answer": "[the] ease",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-yus'ra",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوقِنُونَ",
        "answer": "firmly believe",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yūqinūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوقِنُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) firmly believe",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yūqinūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَيَمَّمُوا",
        "answer": "aim (at)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tayammamū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "267"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَيْمَانِكُمْ",
        "answer": "in your oaths",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "li-aymānikum",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your oaths",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "aymānikum",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and in the Day",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wabil-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a day",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yawman",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامًا",
        "answer": "(for) days",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ayyāman",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a day",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yawman",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "days",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "days",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "days",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "days",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two days",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yawmayni",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "232"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "a Day",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yawmun",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "254"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمًا",
        "answer": "(for) a day",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yawman",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a day",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yawmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "259"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "264"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a Day",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yawman",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "281"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "and (on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامًا",
        "answer": "(Fasting for) days",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "ayyāman",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "212"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "today",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "2",
        "ayah": "249"
    }
]